{"question": "What is a treatment for Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Stanford V", "Cranberry juice", "Lotion", "Epley maneuver"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Cryoablation", "Sulfacytine", "Histamine antagonist", "Photodynamic therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Achilles tendinitis?", "answers": ["Pyrethrin", "Reconstructive surgery", "Orthosis", "Left atrial appendage occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Achilles tendinitis?", "answers": ["Physical exercise", "TNF inhibitor", "Cerivastatin Sodium", "Sulfacytine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Achilles tendinitis?", "answers": ["Angiotensin II receptor antagonist", "Oral rehydration therapy", "Physical therapy", "Pneumococcal vaccine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Achilles tendinitis?", "answers": ["Surgery", "High caloric diet", "Genioglossus advancement", "Kidney transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Perforated eardrum?", "answers": ["Warm compress", "Kegel exercise", "Distraction osteogenesis", "Trabeculoplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Perforated eardrum?", "answers": ["Contact lens", "Stereotactic radiation therapy", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent", "Ear drop"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Perforated eardrum?", "answers": ["Tympanoplasty", "Counseling psychology", "Passive immunity", "Salpingectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Lotion", "Fontan procedure", "Thrombolytic drug", "Antiviral drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiomyopathy?", "answers": ["Lithotripsy", "Cardiac pacemaker", "Capsaicin", "Urethrotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiomyopathy?", "answers": ["Chest tube", "Stretching", "Ablation", "In vitro fertilization"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiomyopathy?", "answers": ["Pyloromyotomy", "Topical steroid", "Lithotripsy", "Defibrillator"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiomyopathy?", "answers": ["Ointment", "Suprapubic cystostomy", "Ventricular assist device", "Pergonal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiomyopathy?", "answers": ["EndoCinch endoluminal gastroplication", "Hormone therapy", "Heart transplantation", "Validation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rosacea?", "answers": ["Sex reassignment surgery", "Hygiene", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent", "Adjuvant"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rosacea?", "answers": ["Carbohydrate", "Oral rehydration therapy", "Soft-tissue laser surgery", "Urinary catheterization"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rosacea?", "answers": ["Vagal maneuver", "Hearing aid", "Electrosurgery", "Negative-pressure wound therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Liver transplantation", "Back brace", "Alcohol detoxification", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Amenorrhoea?", "answers": ["Hydroxyprogesterone", "Vitamin C", "Salpingectomy", "Vitamin E"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Indigestion?", "answers": ["Dextran 75", "Heart transplantation", "Antacid", "Group psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Indigestion?", "answers": ["Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator", "Diet high in omega-3-fatty acids", "Erythritol tetranitrate", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Indigestion?", "answers": ["Prokinetic agent", "Acupuncture", "Liver dialysis", "Alkali salt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Indigestion?", "answers": ["Tonsillectomy", "Antiflatulent", "Anger management", "Pyrithione Zinc"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Spinal stenosis?", "answers": ["Epidural Steroid Injection", "Alpha-adrenergic agonist", "Nephrostomy", "Depigmentation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Spinal stenosis?", "answers": ["Combined oral contraceptive pill", "Dextran 75", "Laminectomy", "Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Spinal stenosis?", "answers": ["Stanford V", "Orthomolecular medicine", "Heat therapy", "Laminotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Spinal stenosis?", "answers": ["Physical examination", "Uterine artery embolization", "Minimally Invasive Thorasic Spinal Fusion", "Breastfeeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Spinal stenosis?", "answers": ["Antifungal medication", "COPP-ABVD Regimen", "Back brace", "Dermabrasion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Spinal stenosis?", "answers": ["Thyroid Agent", "Physical therapy", "Delayed auditory feedback", "Relaxin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Intraocular lens", "Mastoidectomy", "Cold compression therapy", "Immunosuppressive drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Blood glucose monitoring", "Exposure therapy", "Calamine", "Marsupialization"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Antifungal medication", "Zoster-immune globulin", "Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug", "Alcohol detoxification"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Phantom limb?", "answers": ["Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Diet high in omega-3-fatty acids", "Norwood procedure", "Olestra"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "Rubber band ligation", "Ureteric stent", "Diphtheria anti-toxin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Therapeutic endoscopy", "Loop electrical excision procedure", "Antibacterial soap", "Genioglossus advancement"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Trauma Group Therapy", "Clear liquid diet", "Rubber band ligation", "Oral rehydration therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Arthroplasty", "Cholecystectomy", "Embolization", "Lithotripsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Gonadotropin-releasing hormone analogue", "Laser coagulation", "Vein stripping", "Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Antiviral drug", "Pulmonary artery catheter", "Endometrial ablation", "Sun protective clothing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Arthroscopy", "Lung transplantation", "Pergonal", "Uterine artery embolization"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Tonsillectomy", "Assisted reproductive technology", "Cryosurgery", "Hysterectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Anger management", "Plasmapheresis", "Pancreatectomy", "High-intensity focused ultrasound"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Counterirritant", "Uterine myomectomy", "Percutaneous balloon valvotomy", "Needle aponeurotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Club foot?", "answers": ["Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Nerve block", "Orthopedic cast", "Loop electrical excision procedure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Club foot?", "answers": ["Guanadrel", "Defibrillator", "Orabase B", "Stretching"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Club foot?", "answers": ["Orthopedic surgery", "Sanitation", "Topical medication", "Pegylated Interferon Alfa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["SIR-Spheres", "Microvascular decompression", "Liver transplantation", "Catheter ablation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Group psychotherapy", "Cervical conization", "Pegylated Interferon Alfa", "Conception device"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for AIDS?", "answers": ["Management of HIV/AIDS", "Extracorporeal shockwave therapy", "Dextran 75", "Penile prosthesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for AIDS?", "answers": ["Hormone therapy", "Trifocal lenses", "Post-exposure prophylaxis", "Spinal surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scleritis?", "answers": ["SIR-Spheres", "Anti-asthmatic Agent", "Truss", "Immunosuppressant"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Conductive hearing loss?", "answers": ["Anticonvulsant", "Anticonvulsant", "Surgery", "Heat therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Conductive hearing loss?", "answers": ["Cholecystectomy", "Drug detoxification", "Radiofrequency ablation", "Hearing aid"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Conductive hearing loss?", "answers": ["Surgical Drain", "Ear cleaning", "Erythritol tetranitrate", "Uvulopalatopharyngoplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cancer?", "answers": ["Tympanoplasty", "Carotid endarterectomy", "Warm compress", "Chemotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cancer?", "answers": ["Cardiac catheterization", "Surgery", "Debacterol", "Vacuum aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cancer?", "answers": ["TNF inhibitor", "Fluid replacement", "Radiation therapy", "Prosthesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Wilson's disease?", "answers": ["Steroid", "Nasal irrigation", "High fiber diet", "Liver transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Wilson's disease?", "answers": ["Thymectomy", "Scleral buckle", "Triethylenetetramine", "Symptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Canker sore?", "answers": ["Leukotriene antagonist", "Heat therapy", "Calamine", "Debacterol"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Canker sore?", "answers": ["Pergonal", "Renal replacement therapy", "Educational Support Professional", "Orabase B"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Radiation therapy", "Radical perineal prostatectomy", "Hysterectomy", "Vagal maneuver"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Stenting", "Chemotherapy", "Tympanoplasty", "Antibiotic ophthalmic drops"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Immunotherapy", "Circumcision", "Nasal irrigation", "Oophorectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Intravenous immunoglobulin", "BEACOPP", "Surgery", "Nephrostomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Jaundice?", "answers": ["Carotid endarterectomy", "Conductive keratoplasty", "Vitamin B Complex", "Garlic oil"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Jaundice?", "answers": ["Pulmonary rehabilitation", "Cholecystectomy", "Low-fat diet", "Epidural Steroid Injection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Jaundice?", "answers": ["Narcotic", "Low-protein diet", "Pyloromyotomy", "Hydroxyprogesterone"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Jaundice?", "answers": ["Alpha-adrenergic agonist", "Vacuum aspiration", "Surgery", "Cognitive therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pediculosis capitis?", "answers": ["Modifying Phonation Intervals (MPI)", "Curettage", "Dilation and evacuation", "Pyrethrin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Blepharitis?", "answers": ["Cancer immunotherapy", "Laser radial keratotomy", "Pyrethrin", "Proper hygiene"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Blepharitis?", "answers": ["Fontan procedure", "Warm compress", "Vitamin C", "Conductive keratoplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Uterine myomectomy", "Circumcision", "Penile prosthesis", "Sclerotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Fasciotomy", "Proctosedyl", "Monoclonal Antibody Anti-VEGF", "Complete fasciectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Rubber band ligation", "Deep brain stimulation", "PUVA therapy", "Gluten-free diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Corrective lens", "Topical steroid", "Applied behavior analysis", "Fluid replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Graded exercise therapy", "Pneumatic Retinopexy", "Pulmonary Valve Replacement", "Stapled hemorrhoidopexy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Influenza?", "answers": ["Antiviral drug", "Glasses", "Repronex", "High carbohydrate diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Aneurysm?", "answers": ["DizzyFIX", "Low-protein diet", "Cox maze procedure", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atopy?", "answers": ["Embolization", "Stenting", "Immunosuppressive drug", "Anti-asthmatic Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atopy?", "answers": ["Antifungal medication", "Ointment", "Chemotherapy", "Nephrostomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atopy?", "answers": ["Nesbit plication", "Autologous", "Trabeculectomy", "Alkali salt"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Upper respiratory tract infection?", "answers": ["Lithotripsy", "Vicks VapoRub", "Cardioversion", "Vitamin C"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Upper respiratory tract infection?", "answers": ["Increase fluid intake", "Gum depigmentation", "Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug", "Bedrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Upper respiratory tract infection?", "answers": ["Fluency shaping", "Fontan procedure", "Stroke recovery", "Alpha-adrenergic agonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Upper respiratory tract infection?", "answers": ["Maxillomandibular advancement", "Watchful waiting", "Counterirritant", "Rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Spinal Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Endovascular coiling", "Surgery", "Calcium Carbonate", "Acupuncture"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Central pontine myelinolysis?", "answers": ["Clipping", "Intravenous therapy", "Calamine", "Pyrithione Zinc"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Central pontine myelinolysis?", "answers": ["Clear liquid diet", "Arthrocentesis", "Dietary supplement", "Prostate brachytherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Mania?", "answers": ["Histamine antagonist", "Chiropractic treatment techniques", "Nasal irrigation", "Anticonvulsant"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sebaceous cyst?", "answers": ["COPP-ABVD Regimen", "Nail avulsion", "Surgery", "Laminectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sebaceous cyst?", "answers": ["Gum depigmentation", "Alkali salt", "Pyrethrin", "Incision and drainage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sebaceous cyst?", "answers": ["Laser", "Orthokeratology", "Chiropractic treatment techniques", "Prosthesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Inguinal hernia?", "answers": ["Truss", "Tonsillectomy", "Defibrillation", "Light therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Inguinal hernia?", "answers": ["Transcranial direct-current stimulation", "Hernia repair", "Passive immunity", "Traction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Radiation therapy", "Post-exposure prophylaxis", "BEACOPP", "Compression stockings"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Dextran 75", "Prostate brachytherapy", "Blalock\u2013Taussig shunt", "Chemotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Antiviral drug", "Surgery", "Histamine antagonist", "Hip replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Radiosurgery", "Potassium permanganate", "Endovascular aneurysm repair", "Fast neutron therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia?", "answers": ["Antioxidant", "Long-acting beta-adrenoceptor agonist", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Eye drop"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia?", "answers": ["Thoracentesis", "Chemotherapy", "Enema", "Stapled hemorrhoidopexy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for B-cell chronic lymphocytic leukemia?", "answers": ["Counterirritant", "Massage", "Immunotherapy", "Group psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Autism?", "answers": ["Phacoemulsification", "Narcotic", "Orthomolecular medicine", "Suprapubic cystostomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Autism?", "answers": ["Skin grafting", "Speech-language pathology", "High carbohydrate diet", "Prokinetic agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Autism?", "answers": ["Aminobenzoate Potassium", "Applied behavior analysis", "Mastectomy", "Joint replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis management", "Diet high in omega-3-fatty acids", "PUVA therapy", "Bronchodilator"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Smoking cessation", "Joint manipulation", "Ear cleaning", "PUVA therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Physical exercise", "Stenting", "Soft-tissue laser surgery", "Cough medicine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Surgical Drain", "Topical steroid", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Pulmonary rehabilitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute renal failure?", "answers": ["Hemodialysis", "Defibrillation", "Barrier cream", "Corneal transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute renal failure?", "answers": ["Alpha-adrenergic agonist", "Pulmonary artery catheter", "Contact lens", "Soft-tissue laser surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute renal failure?", "answers": ["Antiflatulent", "PUVA therapy", "Intravenous therapy", "In vitro fertilization"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Mallet finger?", "answers": ["Immunotherapy", "Pancreas transplantation", "Surgery", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Mallet finger?", "answers": ["Prostate brachytherapy", "surgery", "Thrombolytic drug", "Splint"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Major depression?", "answers": ["Electroconvulsive therapy", "Continuous positive airway pressure", "Massage", "Bismuth subgallate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Major depression?", "answers": ["Transurethral resection of the prostate", "Diaphragmatic breathing", "Speech-language pathology", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Major depression?", "answers": ["Psychotherapy", "TNF inhibitor", "Gatorade", "BEACOPP"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ebstein's anomaly?", "answers": ["Heart transplantation", "Urethrotomy", "Symptomatic", "Thyroglobulin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Immunotherapy", "Penile prosthesis", "Synovectomy", "Compression stockings"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Chemotherapy", "Debacterol", "Atrial septostomy", "Immunosuppressant"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Radiation therapy", "Dilation and curettage", "Uterine myomectomy", "Bismuth subgallate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Colectomy", "Chiropractic treatment techniques", "Colostomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis D?", "answers": ["Dextran 40", "Stroke recovery", "Low-fat diet", "Percutaneous nephrolithotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis D?", "answers": ["Liver transplantation", "Renal replacement therapy", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis D?", "answers": ["Low-protein diet", "Mitrofanoff appendicovesicostomy", "Arthroscopy", "Steroidal ophthalmic drops"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Calamine", "Oophorectomy", "Alkali salt", "Electrosurgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Radioactive iodine therapy", "Capsaicin", "Palliative care", "Laparoscopic surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Truss", "Artificial tears", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Transsphenoidal surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Chemotherapy", "Soft-tissue laser surgery", "Laser radial keratotomy", "Chloroethane"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Mastectomy", "Bone grafting", "Thyroid Agent", "Pharmacotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Home blood pressure monitors", "Immunotherapy", "Antibiotic ophthalmic drops", "Edmonton protocol"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome?", "answers": ["Heat therapy", "Light therapy", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Plasmapheresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Tuberculosis management", "Pancreas transplantation", "Pulmonary rehabilitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome?", "answers": ["Mechanical ventilation", "Alcohol detoxification", "Tendonectomy", "Coronary stent"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome?", "answers": ["Intracardiac repair", "Cardiac monitoring", "Intravenous immunoglobulin", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Asthma?", "answers": ["Trioxsalen", "Dialectical behavior therapy", "Gum depigmentation", "Bronchodilator"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Asthma?", "answers": ["Vicks VapoRub", "Long-acting beta-adrenoceptor agonist", "Aminobenzoate Potassium", "Antifungal medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Asthma?", "answers": ["Trauma Group Therapy", "Capsaicin", "Contact lens", "Anti-asthmatic Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hyperparathyroidism?", "answers": ["In vitro fertilization", "Incision and drainage", "Esophagogastrectomy", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hyperparathyroidism?", "answers": ["Smoking cessation", "Lactase", "Hormone replacement therapy", "Refractive surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Mechanical ventilation", "Stenting", "Thrombectomy", "Synovectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Ureteroscopic stone removal", "Proper hygiene", "Dextran 1", "Smoking cessation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Pulmonary artery catheter", "Bed rest", "Pancreaticoduodenectomy", "Coronary artery bypass surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Appendectomy", "Weight loss", "Alcohol detoxification", "Tendonectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Mustargen Oncovin Procarbazine Prednisone", "Pentaerythritol", "Intracardiac repair", "Esophagogastrectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Erythritol tetranitrate", "Fast neutron therapy", "Cardiac surgery", "Dextran 40"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Trioxsalen", "Angioplasty", "Thyroidectomy", "Reconstructive surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastritis?", "answers": ["Intracardiac repair", "Antacid", "Catheter ablation therapy", "Massage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Testicular cancer?", "answers": ["Inguinal orchiectomy", "Chemoembolization", "Thyroid Agent", "Hormone therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Testicular cancer?", "answers": ["Long-acting beta-adrenoceptor agonist", "Surgical Drain", "Chemotherapy", "surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Testicular cancer?", "answers": ["Transurethral microwave thermotherapy", "Trabeculoplasty", "Urethroplasty", "Retroperitoneal lymph node dissection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Testicular cancer?", "answers": ["Move patient to cool area", "Hormone therapy", "Radiation therapy", "Prokinetic agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Fetal alcohol syndrome?", "answers": ["Special education", "Counseling", "Narcotic", "Cholecystectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Fetal alcohol syndrome?", "answers": ["Counseling psychology", "Dialectical behavior therapy", "Antacid", "Hormone replacement therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Albinism?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Trioxsalen", "Sunscreen", "Steroidal ophthalmic drops"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dental caries?", "answers": ["Sensory integration", "Dental restoration", "Radial keratotomy", "Orabase B"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bell's palsy?", "answers": ["Modifying Phonation Intervals (MPI)", "Eyepatch", "Selective estrogen-receptor modulator", "Pyloromyotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bell's palsy?", "answers": ["Relaxation technique", "Thyroglobulin", "External beam radiotherapy", "Eye drop"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Polymorphous light eruption?", "answers": ["Sun protective clothing", "Acupuncture", "Rehydration", "Cyanate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Polymorphous light eruption?", "answers": ["Cognitive therapy", "Mechanical ventilation", "Sunscreen", "Phacoemulsification"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Erythema nodosum?", "answers": ["Fluid replacement", "Nephrostomy", "Bedrest", "Adrenalectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Thyroidectomy", "Lung transplantation", "Distraction osteogenesis", "Proctocolectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Cardiac monitoring", "External beam radiotherapy", "Fluency shaping", "Cholecystectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Anti-diabetic medication", "Surgery", "Traction", "Alcohol detoxification"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Lobectomy", "Carotid endarterectomy", "Orthopedic cast", "SIR-Spheres"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Radiation therapy", "Ear drop", "Vitamin C", "Antiandrogen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Enema", "Scleral buckle", "Dextran 40", "Hormone therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Heat therapy", "Physical exercise", "Antibacterial soap", "Thyroglobulin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Gonadotropin-releasing hormone analogue", "Low sodium diet", "Pulmonary artery catheter", "Radioactive iodine therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Alpha-adrenergic agonist", "Genioglossus advancement", "Cranberry juice", "Chemotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Placenta praevia?", "answers": ["High-intensity focused ultrasound", "Antiplatelet drug", "Exposure therapy", "Bed rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Placenta praevia?", "answers": ["Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy", "Caesarean section", "Physical exercise", "Graded exercise therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Corneal abrasion?", "answers": ["Antibiotic ophthalmic drops", "Laminotomy", "Nissen fundoplication", "Low sodium diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Corneal abrasion?", "answers": ["Debacterol", "Phototherapeutic keratectomy", "Triethylenetetramine", "Proper hygiene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Artificial tears", "Laparoscopic surgery", "Urinary catheterization", "Colectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Cancer immunotherapy", "Salpingectomy", "SIR-Spheres"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Anticonvulsant", "Alkali salt", "Renal replacement therapy", "Lithotripsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Artificial tears", "Chest tube", "Complete fasciectomy", "Psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Laryngitis?", "answers": ["Endovascular coiling", "Throat lozenge", "Partial Thyroidectomy", "Wide local excision"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Laryngitis?", "answers": ["Psychoeducation", "Endometrial ablation", "Rest", "Traction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Laryngitis?", "answers": ["Polypectomy", "Management of HIV/AIDS", "Dietary supplement", "Speech-language pathology"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Laryngitis?", "answers": ["Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation", "Hemodialysis", "Self-limiting", "Antifungal medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastric dumping syndrome?", "answers": ["Blood transfusion", "Anti-asthmatic Agent", "Surgery", "Carotid endarterectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Olestra", "Frequency-altered auditory feedback", "Cervical conization", "Anti-diabetic medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Parathyroidectomy", "High-intensity focused ultrasound", "Diabetic diet", "Bonjela"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Osteotomy", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Physical exercise", "Vagus nerve stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Cryosurgery", "Joint replacement", "Synovectomy", "Smoking cessation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Osteotomy", "Carotid endarterectomy", "Physical examination", "Circumcision"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cystitis?", "answers": ["External beam radiotherapy", "Laparoscopic surgery", "Trimethoprim-Sulfamethoxazole", "Steroid"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Immunosuppressant", "Antifungal medication", "Immunosuppressive drug", "Prokinetic agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Sensory integration", "Esophagogastrectomy", "Vitamin E", "Psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Laparoscopic radical prostatectomy", "Chemotherapy", "Hernia repair", "Electroconvulsive therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Hormone replacement therapy", "Cataract surgery", "Surgery", "Renal replacement therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Surgical Drain", "Smoking cessation", "Monoclonal Antibody Anti-VEGF", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Smoking cessation", "Capsaicin", "Esophagectomy", "Cochlear implant"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Photodynamic therapy", "Graded exercise therapy", "Renal replacement therapy", "Modifying Phonation Intervals (MPI)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pyloric stenosis?", "answers": ["Oxygen therapy", "Laparoscopic surgery", "Neurectomy", "Panretinal Photocoagulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pyloric stenosis?", "answers": ["Hydroxyprogesterone", "Thrombolytic drug", "Rubber band ligation", "Intravenous therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pyloric stenosis?", "answers": ["Gene therapy", "Dextran 1", "Incision and drainage", "Pyloromyotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Molluscum contagiosum?", "answers": ["Abstinence", "Mustargen Oncovin Procarbazine Prednisone", "Steroid", "Repronex"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Molluscum contagiosum?", "answers": ["Catheter ablation therapy", "Transsphenoidal surgery", "High carbohydrate diet", "Curettage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Molluscum contagiosum?", "answers": ["Narcotic", "Turbinectomy", "Lotion", "Esophagectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Molluscum contagiosum?", "answers": ["Reminiscence therapy", "Norwood procedure", "Ultraviolet light therapy", "Cryotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Plasmapheresis", "Debridement", "Transurethral resection of the prostate", "Cerivastatin Sodium"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Steroidal ophthalmic drops", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent", "Occupational therapy", "Uterine artery embolization"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Antiplatelet drug", "Assisted reproductive technology", "Physical therapy", "Dental restoration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pyogenic granuloma?", "answers": ["Cox maze procedure", "Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Cauterization", "Physical medicine and rehabilitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pyogenic granuloma?", "answers": ["Compression stockings", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate", "Laser radial keratotomy", "Laser therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pyogenic granuloma?", "answers": ["Cryotherapy", "Parathyroidectomy", "Panretinal Photocoagulation", "Simulated presence therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cleft Palate?", "answers": ["Nail avulsion", "Turbinectomy", "Reconstructive surgery", "Electroconvulsive therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cleft Palate?", "answers": ["Nephrostomy", "Renal replacement therapy", "Prosthesis", "Stereotactic radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cleft Palate?", "answers": ["Speech-language pathology", "Adjuvant", "Minimally Invasive Thorasic Spinal Fusion", "Epidural Steroid Injection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cleft Palate?", "answers": ["Ureteric stent", "Psychotherapy", "Ultraviolet light therapy", "Dextran 75"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Neonatal jaundice?", "answers": ["Orthosis", "Breastfeeding", "Orthosis", "Electroconvulsive therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Neonatal jaundice?", "answers": ["Maxillomandibular advancement", "Kegel exercise", "Scleral buckle", "Blood transfusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Neonatal jaundice?", "answers": ["Speech-language pathology", "Repronex", "Light therapy", "Topical medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Restless legs syndrome?", "answers": ["Thoracentesis", "Smoking cessation", "Iridectomy", "Immunotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Restless legs syndrome?", "answers": ["Escharotomy", "Psychotherapy", "Cold compression therapy", "Endovenous laser treatment"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Restless legs syndrome?", "answers": ["Rest", "Defibrillation", "Warm compress", "Frequency-altered auditory feedback"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Restless legs syndrome?", "answers": ["Pancreatectomy", "Physical exercise", "Dietary fiber", "Cardiac pacemaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Restless legs syndrome?", "answers": ["High-intensity focused ultrasound", "Relaxation technique", "Ice pack", "Aortic valve replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Restless legs syndrome?", "answers": ["Massage", "Thyroglobulin", "Pulmonary rehabilitation", "Liposomal doxorubicin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Headache?", "answers": ["Enucleation of the eye", "Cefaly", "Nicotine withdrawal", "Reconstructive surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alcoholic hepatitis?", "answers": ["Liver transplantation", "Radial keratotomy", "Thyroglobulin", "Mastectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alcoholic hepatitis?", "answers": ["Low-fat diet", "Transurethral needle ablation of the prostate", "Tuberculosis management", "Bronchodilator"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alcoholic hepatitis?", "answers": ["Low-protein diet", "Pergonal", "SIR-Spheres", "Endovascular aneurysm repair"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hidradenitis suppurativa?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Debridement", "Wide local excision", "Laparotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hidradenitis suppurativa?", "answers": ["Soft-tissue laser surgery", "Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug", "Clear liquid diet", "Bonjela"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hidradenitis suppurativa?", "answers": ["Chemoembolization", "Mastectomy", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent", "Incision and drainage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteomyelitis?", "answers": ["Thrombectomy", "Stroke recovery", "Bone grafting", "Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteomyelitis?", "answers": ["Nasal spray", "Laser", "Counterirritant", "Incision and drainage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteomyelitis?", "answers": ["Home blood pressure monitors", "Debridement", "Move patient to cool area", "Low sodium diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteomyelitis?", "answers": ["Palliative care", "Subtotal Parathyroidectomy", "Surgery", "Breastfeeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bulimia nervosa?", "answers": ["Extracorporeal shockwave therapy", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Stress management", "Needle aponeurotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Mood disorder?", "answers": ["Orthomolecular medicine", "Surgery", "Home blood pressure monitors", "Bone grafting"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoporosis?", "answers": ["Dietary fiber", "Laser", "Cardiac pacemaker", "Physical exercise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoporosis?", "answers": ["Hormone replacement therapy", "Pneumococcal vaccine", "Immunosuppressive drug", "Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoporosis?", "answers": ["Physical medicine and rehabilitation", "Fluency shaping", "Phacoemulsification", "Selective estrogen-receptor modulator"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tourette syndrome?", "answers": ["Stretching", "Vagus nerve stimulation", "Percutaneous Ethanol Injection", "Deep brain stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tourette syndrome?", "answers": ["Plasmapheresis", "Patellar tendon strap", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Laser radial keratotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tertiary hyperparathyroidism?", "answers": ["Subtotal Parathyroidectomy", "Thoracentesis", "Family Therapy", "Intraocular lens"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tertiary hyperparathyroidism?", "answers": ["Dental restoration", "Parathyroidectomy", "Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Reminiscence therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dengue fever?", "answers": ["BEACOPP", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Fontan procedure", "Fluid replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Polypectomy", "Colostomy", "Vicks VapoRub", "Rehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Skin cancer?", "answers": ["Artificial tears", "Moisturizer", "Tendonectomy", "Cryosurgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Skin cancer?", "answers": ["Mohs surgery", "Alpha-adrenergic agonist", "Diphenidol", "Throat lozenge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Skin cancer?", "answers": ["Radiation therapy", "Respiratory therapy", "Gum depigmentation", "Oophorectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myasthenia gravis?", "answers": ["Plasmapheresis", "Psychoeducation", "Cochlear implant", "Family Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myasthenia gravis?", "answers": ["Transsphenoidal surgery", "Traction", "Tendonectomy", "Mycophenolate Mofetil"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myasthenia gravis?", "answers": ["Sulfacytine", "Autologous", "Thymectomy", "Electrical muscle stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myasthenia gravis?", "answers": ["Liver transplantation", "Autologous", "Intravenous immunoglobulin", "In vitro fertilization"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bladder cancer?", "answers": ["Family Therapy", "Reconstructive surgery", "Chemotherapy", "Family Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bladder cancer?", "answers": ["Gonadotropin-releasing hormone analogue", "Cancer immunotherapy", "Percutaneous trigger finger release", "High caloric diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bladder cancer?", "answers": ["Radiation therapy", "Tuboplasty", "Management of HIV/AIDS", "Androgen replacement therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bladder cancer?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Laminotomy", "Escharotomy", "surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Metabolic syndrome?", "answers": ["Psychoeducation", "Dextran 40", "Smoking cessation", "Left atrial appendage occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Onychocryptosis?", "answers": ["Inguinal orchiectomy", "Warm soak", "Childbirth", "Carbohydrate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Onychocryptosis?", "answers": ["Fast neutron therapy", "Nail avulsion", "Extracorporeal shockwave therapy", "Elastic bandage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tetralogy of Fallot?", "answers": ["Vitamin B Complex", "Ureteric stent", "Intracardiac repair", "Escharotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tetralogy of Fallot?", "answers": ["Caesarean section", "Blalock\u2013Taussig shunt", "Psychoeducation", "Proctosedyl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Intracytoplasmic sperm injection", "Complete fasciectomy", "Chiropractic treatment techniques", "Stress management"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Laminectomy", "Cardiac surgery", "Steroidal ophthalmic drops", "Vicks VapoRub"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Speech-language pathology", "Low-fat diet", "Left atrial appendage occlusion", "Thrombolytic drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Alkali salt", "Percutaneous Ethanol Injection", "Laser radial keratotomy", "Cardioversion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Low sodium diet", "Clear liquid diet", "Carbohydrate", "Endoscopic thoracic sympathectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Antiarrhythmic agent", "Retroperitoneal lymph node dissection", "Vitamin B Complex", "Lotion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Iron supplement", "Self-limiting", "High carbohydrate diet", "Enucleation of the eye"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Cognitive remediation therapy for schizophrenia", "Partial fasciectomy", "Liver transplantation", "Exposure therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Alcohol detoxification", "Bowel resection", "Low sodium diet", "Turbinectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Cryosurgery", "Steroidal ophthalmic drops", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Low-protein diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Repronex", "Intravenous therapy", "Antifungal medication", "Renal replacement therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Special education", "Vagal maneuver", "Antacid", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Cardiac catheterization", "Vitamin E", "Spinal cord stimulator", "Kidney transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Antiflatulent", "Percutaneous trigger finger release", "Dialysis", "Rehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Blood transfusion", "Self-limiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["High fiber diet", "Chloroethane", "Spinal surgery", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hemispatial neglect?", "answers": ["Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Reconstructive surgery", "Atrial septostomy", "Microvascular decompression"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Mouth ulcer?", "answers": ["Home blood pressure monitors", "Electroconvulsive therapy", "Bonjela", "Applied behavior analysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Meningococcal disease?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "Electrical muscle stimulation", "Myringotomy", "Angioplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obstructive uropathy?", "answers": ["Nephrostomy", "Negative-pressure wound therapy", "Median sternotomy", "Intraocular lens"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obstructive uropathy?", "answers": ["Orabase B", "Ventricular assist device", "Occupational therapy", "Lithotripsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obstructive uropathy?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Sensory integration", "Panretinal Photocoagulation", "Incision and drainage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obstructive uropathy?", "answers": ["Bed rest", "Pyrethrin", "Urinary catheterization", "Leriche Technique"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Conception device", "Gluten-free diet", "Conception device", "Tympanoplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gout?", "answers": ["Hydrodilatation", "Ointment", "EndoCinch endoluminal gastroplication", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scleroderma?", "answers": ["Antiplatelet drug", "Laser", "Lung transplantation", "Blalock\u2013Taussig shunt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scleroderma?", "answers": ["Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Marsupialization", "Retroperitoneal lymph node dissection", "Oxygen therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scleroderma?", "answers": ["Calcium Carbonate", "Amputation", "Immunosuppressant", "Low-protein diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scleroderma?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Low-fat diet", "Oophorectomy", "Left atrial appendage occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scleroderma?", "answers": ["Extracorporeal shockwave therapy", "Vicks VapoRub", "Dental restoration", "Relaxin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scleroderma?", "answers": ["Smoking cessation", "Eyepatch", "PUVA therapy", "Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Red eye?", "answers": ["Cold compression therapy", "Antifungal medication", "Occupational therapy", "PUVA therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Red eye?", "answers": ["Gene therapy", "Iron supplement", "Artificial tears", "Hemodialysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Red eye?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Lactase", "Vasoconstrictor", "Antioxidant"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Thyroglobulin", "Respiratory therapy", "Hydrodilatation", "Physical exercise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Nesbit plication", "Moisturizer", "Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Fast neutron therapy", "Barrier cream", "Dental restoration", "Low-fat diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Edmonton protocol", "Counseling psychology", "Low-carbohydrate diet", "Antifungal medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Astigmatism?", "answers": ["Therapeutic endoscopy", "Stretta system", "Proctocolectomy", "Photorefractive keratectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Astigmatism?", "answers": ["Stretching", "Contact lens", "Stapled hemorrhoidopexy", "Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Astigmatism?", "answers": ["LASIK", "Antiplatelet drug", "Liposuction", "Gene therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Astigmatism?", "answers": ["Glasses", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "High-intensity focused ultrasound", "Conductive keratoplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Substance-related disorder?", "answers": ["Caesarean section", "Therapeutic endoscopy", "Counseling", "Bonjela"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Substance-related disorder?", "answers": ["Cryoablation", "Transsphenoidal surgery", "Orthomolecular medicine", "Drug detoxification"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Substance-related disorder?", "answers": ["Support group", "Tuberculosis management", "Colostomy", "Garlic oil"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cerebral palsy?", "answers": ["Needle aponeurotomy", "Nissen fundoplication", "Occupational therapy", "Warm soak"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cerebral palsy?", "answers": ["Orthopedic surgery", "Liposuction", "Uvulopalatopharyngoplasty", "Cardiac catheterization"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cerebral palsy?", "answers": ["Marsupialization", "Sodium hyaluronate", "Corrective lens", "Physical therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cerebral palsy?", "answers": ["Relaxation technique", "Heart transplantation", "Anticonvulsant", "Prosthesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cerebral palsy?", "answers": ["Neurectomy", "Topical medication", "Loop electrical excision procedure", "Hemodialysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cerebral palsy?", "answers": ["Simulated presence therapy", "Surgery", "Bifocals", "Kegel exercise"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cerebral palsy?", "answers": ["Speech-language pathology", "Self-limiting", "Long-acting beta-adrenoceptor agonist", "Conception device"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Oral rehydration therapy", "Thrombolytic drug", "Splint", "Implanted cardiac resynchronization device"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Papillary thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["POWERade", "Hormone therapy", "Blood glucose monitoring", "Percutaneous nephrolithotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Papillary thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Management of HIV/AIDS", "Contact lens", "Ureteric stent", "Radioactive iodine therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Papillary thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Counseling psychology", "Chemotherapy", "Vein stripping", "Iridectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Papillary thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Radiation therapy", "Trimethoprim-Sulfamethoxazole", "Antiflatulent", "Defibrillation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Papillary thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Drug detoxification", "Debacterol", "Gluten-free diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ureterocele?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Tuberculosis management", "Support group", "Stretta system"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypoparathyroidism?", "answers": ["Kawashima procedure", "Anticonvulsant", "Mitrofanoff appendicovesicostomy", "Calcium Carbonate"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dehydration?", "answers": ["Endoscopic thoracic sympathectomy", "Tonsillectomy", "Rehydration", "Incision and drainage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tendonitis?", "answers": ["High carbohydrate diet", "Physical therapy", "Fungicide", "Immunosuppressant"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lactose intolerance?", "answers": ["Lactase", "Cholinesterase inhibitor", "Uterine myomectomy", "High-intensity focused ultrasound"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Wolff\u2013Parkinson\u2013White syndrome?", "answers": ["Catheter ablation therapy", "Laparoscopic radical prostatectomy", "Transurethral needle ablation of the prostate", "Intravenous immunoglobulin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chalazion?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Clipping", "Cervical conization", "Mastoidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chalazion?", "answers": ["Bismuth subgallate", "Proper hygiene", "Pyrithione Zinc", "Enema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chalazion?", "answers": ["Warm compress", "Chemotherapy", "Rehabilitation", "Immunosuppressive drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obesity?", "answers": ["Laparotomy", "Pharmacotherapy", "Laser", "High fiber diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obesity?", "answers": ["Counseling psychology", "Caesarean section", "Warm compress", "Olestra"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obesity?", "answers": ["Inguinal orchiectomy", "Antibacterial soap", "Laminotomy", "Bariatric surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obesity?", "answers": ["Penile prosthesis", "Transsphenoidal surgery", "Low-fat diet", "Alcohol detoxification"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obesity?", "answers": ["Artificial tears", "Gluten-free diet", "Wide local excision", "Physical exercise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Cerivastatin Sodium", "Pulmonary Valve Replacement", "Mechanical ventilation", "Sun protective clothing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Arthroscopy", "Transcranial direct-current stimulation", "Artificial tears", "Speech-language pathology"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Hemodialysis", "Incision and drainage", "Physical therapy", "Laparoscopic radical prostatectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Leukotriene antagonist", "Pancreaticoduodenectomy", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Simulated presence therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Occupational therapy", "Thyroglobulin", "Trioxsalen", "Antibiotic ophthalmic drops"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Medullary thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Potassium permanganate", "Chemotherapy", "Hormone replacement therapy", "Trioxsalen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Medullary thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Prokinetic agent", "Radiation therapy", "Pericardiocentesis", "Vagus nerve stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Medullary thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Hormone therapy", "Autologous", "Transurethral resection of the prostate", "Biofeedback"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Medullary thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Antibacterial soap", "Orthosis", "Deep brain stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Medullary thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Olestra", "High-intensity focused ultrasound", "Hospitalization", "Thyroidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Enteritis?", "answers": ["Iron supplement", "Stanford V", "Self-limiting", "High carbohydrate diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Enteritis?", "answers": ["Hearing aid", "Intracardiac repair", "Ice pack", "Oral rehydration therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Heart failure?", "answers": ["Ear drop", "Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Cognitive remediation therapy for schizophrenia", "Proper hygiene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Heart failure?", "answers": ["Median sternotomy", "Vagus nerve stimulation", "Olestra", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Heart failure?", "answers": ["Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy", "Wide local excision", "Left Ventricular Assist Device", "Antiviral drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Heart failure?", "answers": ["Biologic", "Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator", "LASIK", "Lotion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Vascular malformation?", "answers": ["Pulmonary artery catheter", "Pericardiocentesis", "Ketogenic diet", "Radiosurgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Vascular malformation?", "answers": ["Chemoembolization", "Exposure therapy", "Embolization", "Cardiac monitoring"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Vascular malformation?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Thyroglobulin", "Orabase B", "Intravenous therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Balance disorder?", "answers": ["Cough medicine", "Animal-assisted therapy", "Tuberculosis management", "Low sodium diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Balance disorder?", "answers": ["Corneal transplantation", "Surgery", "Tuboplasty", "Vitamin B Complex"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Balance disorder?", "answers": ["Immunosuppressive drug", "Nicotine withdrawal", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Myringotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Retinoblastoma?", "answers": ["Corrective lens", "Reconstructive surgery", "Androgen replacement therapy", "Cryotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Retinoblastoma?", "answers": ["Calcium levulinate", "Proper hygiene", "Lactase", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Retinoblastoma?", "answers": ["Mitral valve repair", "Trioxsalen", "Enucleation of the eye", "Antiflatulent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Amblyopia?", "answers": ["Corrective lens", "Prostate brachytherapy", "POWERade", "Proctocolectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Amblyopia?", "answers": ["Thymectomy", "Eyepatch", "Brachytherapy", "Low-carbohydrate diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Amblyopia?", "answers": ["Dietary supplement", "Eye surgery", "Balloon  valvuloplasty", "Elevation of the legs"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Amblyopia?", "answers": ["POWERade", "Diphenidol", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Dilation and curettage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Radical retropubic prostatectomy", "Joint replacement", "Hormone therapy", "Intra-aortic balloon pump"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Cancer immunotherapy", "Cough medicine", "Artificial tears", "LASIK"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Intrastromal corneal ring segments", "Thrombolytic drug", "Gluten-free diet", "Mastectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Antiandrogen", "Nail avulsion", "TNF inhibitor", "Chemotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Dilation and evacuation", "Radiation therapy", "Laxative", "Nightmare Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Infertility?", "answers": ["Occupational therapy", "Surgery", "Pancreatectomy", "Throat lozenge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Infertility?", "answers": ["Percutaneous coronary intervention", "Liver dialysis", "Cryotherapy", "Repronex"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Infertility?", "answers": ["Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy", "Patellar tendon strap", "Assisted reproductive technology", "Skin grafting"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Infertility?", "answers": ["Validation therapy", "Counseling", "Tuboplasty", "Moisturizer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Infertility?", "answers": ["Inguinal orchiectomy", "Relaxin", "Intracytoplasmic sperm injection", "Physical exercise"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Infertility?", "answers": ["Artificial tears", "Conception device", "Left Ventricular Assist Device", "Orthopedic surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Infertility?", "answers": ["Coronary stent", "Bowel resection", "Clipping", "In vitro fertilization"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Infertility?", "answers": ["Chemoembolization", "Pericardiocentesis", "Nil per os", "Gonadotropin-releasing hormone analogue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Laser therapy", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Minimally Invasive Thorasic Spinal Fusion", "Genioglossus advancement"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Ear drop", "Atrial septostomy", "Mustargen Oncovin Procarbazine Prednisone", "Nil per os"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Ventricular assist device", "Prokinetic agent", "Radiation therapy", "Sclerotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Stanford V", "Pegylated Interferon Alfa", "Hysterectomy", "Calcium levulinate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Corneal transplantation", "Epley maneuver", "BEACOPP", "Sun protective clothing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Diaphragmatic breathing", "Erythritol tetranitrate", "COPP-ABVD Regimen", "Simulated presence therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Otitis media?", "answers": ["Splint", "Monoclonal Antibody Anti-VEGF", "Tympanostomy tube", "Lobectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Otitis media?", "answers": ["Hearing aid", "Cough medicine", "Myringotomy", "Narcotic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Perinatal asphyxia?", "answers": ["COPP-ABVD Regimen", "Oxygen therapy", "Cryosurgery", "Chest tube"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Perinatal asphyxia?", "answers": ["Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Enema", "Nerve block", "Caesarean section"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Perinatal asphyxia?", "answers": ["Eye surgery", "Antioxidant", "Mechanical ventilation", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Persistent truncus arteriosus?", "answers": ["Radioactive iodine therapy", "Hysterectomy", "Cognitive therapy", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pleurisy?", "answers": ["Epidural Steroid Injection", "Pyloromyotomy", "Thoracentesis", "Reconstructive surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Complex regional pain syndrome?", "answers": ["Atrial septostomy", "Sensory integration", "Hearing aid", "Physical therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Complex regional pain syndrome?", "answers": ["Acupuncture", "Endoscopic thoracic sympathectomy", "In vitro fertilization", "Stenting"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Complex regional pain syndrome?", "answers": ["Nerve block", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Symptomatic", "Increase fluid intake"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Complex regional pain syndrome?", "answers": ["Circumcision", "Uterine artery embolization", "Spinal cord stimulator", "Dextrothyroxine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Complex regional pain syndrome?", "answers": ["Vitamin B Complex", "Pergonal", "Hydrodilatation", "Occupational therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Complex regional pain syndrome?", "answers": ["Polypectomy", "Biofeedback", "Cardiac catheterization", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Complex regional pain syndrome?", "answers": ["Intraocular lens", "Kawashima procedure", "Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation", "External beam radiotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Varicose veins?", "answers": ["Uvulopalatopharyngoplasty", "Sclerotherapy", "Debridement", "Leriche Technique"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Varicose veins?", "answers": ["Assisted reproductive technology", "Myringotomy", "Hemodialysis", "Elevation of the legs"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Varicose veins?", "answers": ["Abstinence", "Radial keratotomy", "Thrombectomy", "Radiofrequency ablation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Varicose veins?", "answers": ["Pneumococcal vaccine", "PUVA therapy", "Histamine antagonist", "Endovenous laser treatment"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Varicose veins?", "answers": ["Hearing aid", "Cold compression therapy", "Compression stockings", "Trabeculoplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Varicose veins?", "answers": ["Vein stripping", "Phacoemulsification", "Anti-asthmatic Agent", "Pneumatic Retinopexy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Varicose veins?", "answers": ["Brachytherapy", "Special education", "Ambulatory phlebectomy", "Pegylated Interferon Alfa"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Jet lag?", "answers": ["Acupuncture", "Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy", "Thyroid Agent", "Light therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Carpal tunnel syndrome?", "answers": ["Edmonton protocol", "Wide local excision", "Splint", "Palliative care"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Carpal tunnel syndrome?", "answers": ["Orthopedic cast", "Chemotherapy", "Surgery", "Adrenalectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stevens\u2013Johnson syndrome?", "answers": ["TNF inhibitor", "Cholecystectomy", "Rehydration", "Cataract surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Intracranial aneurysm?", "answers": ["Moisturizer", "Physical medicine and rehabilitation", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist", "Tendonectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Intracranial aneurysm?", "answers": ["Educational Support Professional", "Truss", "Cognitive therapy", "Endovascular coiling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Intracranial aneurysm?", "answers": ["Calcium Carbonate", "Clipping", "Aminobenzoate Potassium", "SIR-Spheres"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Intracranial aneurysm?", "answers": ["Antibacterial soap", "Anticonvulsant", "Low-carbohydrate diet", "Incision and drainage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Supraventricular tachycardia?", "answers": ["Catheter ablation therapy", "Transurethral needle ablation of the prostate", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist", "Hydrodilatation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pectus excavatum?", "answers": ["Arthroscopy", "Cognitive remediation therapy for schizophrenia", "Vagal maneuver", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hydronephrosis?", "answers": ["High carbohydrate diet", "Orthomolecular medicine", "Urinary catheterization", "Diet high in omega-3-fatty acids"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hydronephrosis?", "answers": ["Ablation", "Gatorade", "Embolization", "Suprapubic cystostomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hydronephrosis?", "answers": ["Ureteric stent", "Vitamin C", "Westmead Program", "Thrombectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hydronephrosis?", "answers": ["Nephrostomy", "External beam radiotherapy", "Bifocals", "Intravenous immunoglobulin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hydronephrosis?", "answers": ["POWERade", "Counseling", "Pyeloplasty", "Mastoidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hydronephrosis?", "answers": ["Stereotactic radiation therapy", "Surgery", "Occupational therapy", "Nightmare Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Miscarriage?", "answers": ["Endometrial ablation", "Dilation and curettage", "Electrical muscle stimulation", "Microvascular decompression"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Miscarriage?", "answers": ["Support group", "Vacuum aspiration", "Warm soak", "Gonadotropin-releasing hormone analogue"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Miscarriage?", "answers": ["Potassium permanganate", "Arthrocentesis", "Dilation and evacuation", "Anti-asthmatic Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Miscarriage?", "answers": ["Bedrest", "LASIK", "Ice pack", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rett syndrome?", "answers": ["Panretinal Photocoagulation", "Animal-assisted therapy", "Nutrition", "Ablation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rett syndrome?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Defibrillator", "Biofeedback", "Cognitive remediation therapy for schizophrenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rett syndrome?", "answers": ["Thrombolytic drug", "Self-limiting", "Spinal cord stimulator", "Speech-language pathology"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rett syndrome?", "answers": ["Post-exposure prophylaxis", "Colectomy", "Needle aponeurotomy", "Anticonvulsant"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pain disorder?", "answers": ["Aortic valve replacement", "Brachytherapy", "Physical therapy", "Transurethral microwave thermotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pain disorder?", "answers": ["Tracheotomy", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Patellar tendon strap", "Leriche Technique"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pain disorder?", "answers": ["Joint manipulation", "Family Therapy", "Genioglossus advancement", "Hyperbaric medicine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Eczema?", "answers": ["Traction", "Immunosuppressive drug", "Relaxation technique", "Eyepatch"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anaplastic thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Cardioversion", "Laser therapy", "Orthosis", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anaplastic thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Diabetic diet", "Laxative", "Thyroidectomy", "Steroidal ophthalmic drops"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anaplastic thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate", "Chemotherapy", "Gradual increase in length and complexity of utterance (GILCU)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anaplastic thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Vagus nerve stimulation", "Soft-tissue laser surgery", "Surgery", "Rehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Urethrotomy", "Cognitive remediation therapy for schizophrenia", "Tendonectomy", "Hospitalization"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Family Therapy", "Rubber band ligation", "Dextrothyroxine", "Anticonvulsant"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Fast neutron therapy", "Rehydration", "Bifocals", "Laparoscopic radical prostatectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Hydroxyprogesterone", "Psychotherapy", "COPP-ABVD Regimen", "Relaxin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acne?", "answers": ["Colostomy", "Heart transplantation", "Dermabrasion", "Heart transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acne?", "answers": ["Laser", "Orabase B", "Modifying Phonation Intervals (MPI)", "Vitamin C"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acne?", "answers": ["Graded exercise therapy", "Sclerotherapy", "Combined oral contraceptive pill", "Diphtheria anti-toxin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acne?", "answers": ["Electrosurgery", "Bifocals", "Tuberculosis management", "Antibacterial soap"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acne?", "answers": ["Lung transplantation", "Steroidal ophthalmic drops", "Alkali salt", "Topical medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acne?", "answers": ["Photodynamic therapy", "Low sodium diet", "Uterine artery embolization", "Pegylated Interferon Alfa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acne?", "answers": ["Thyroid Agent", "Distraction osteogenesis", "Light therapy", "Osteotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Increase fluid intake", "Radiation therapy", "Incision and drainage", "Lung transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Nasal irrigation", "Complete fasciectomy", "Clipping", "Pulmonary Valve Replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Arthroscopy", "Pericardiocentesis", "Cholecystectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Migraine?", "answers": ["Triethylenetetramine", "Cerivastatin Sodium", "Graded exercise therapy", "Cefaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Migraine?", "answers": ["Ignipuncture", "Cardioversion", "Mastoidectomy", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Amoebiasis?", "answers": ["Topical steroid", "Nasal spray", "Nicotine withdrawal", "Oral rehydration therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pressure ulcer?", "answers": ["Stroke recovery", "Counterirritant", "Splint", "Low sodium diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pressure ulcer?", "answers": ["Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate", "Surgery", "Chest tube", "Edmonton protocol"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pressure ulcer?", "answers": ["Debridement", "Amputation", "Cryotherapy", "Biologic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pressure ulcer?", "answers": ["Management of HIV/AIDS", "Clipping", "DizzyFIX", "Hydrotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sickle cell disease?", "answers": ["Cyanate", "Home blood pressure monitors", "Coronary stent", "Antifungal medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sickle cell disease?", "answers": ["Occupational therapy", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Tracheotomy", "Thymectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Melanoma?", "answers": ["Chemotherapy", "Contact lens", "Cardiac catheterization", "Diphenidol"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Melanoma?", "answers": ["Cardiac pacemaker", "Surgery", "Lung transplantation", "Endovascular coiling"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Melanoma?", "answers": ["Zoster-immune globulin", "Exposure therapy", "Stretching", "Immunotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Melanoma?", "answers": ["Radiation therapy", "Tympanoplasty", "Arthroplasty", "Cardiac catheterization"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adhesive capsulitis of shoulder?", "answers": ["Acupuncture", "Radiofrequency ablation", "Joint replacement", "Electrical muscle stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adhesive capsulitis of shoulder?", "answers": ["Arthroscopy", "Diphenidol", "Ureteric stent", "Tympanostomy tube"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adhesive capsulitis of shoulder?", "answers": ["Rest", "Spinal cord stimulator", "Hydrodilatation", "Physical medicine and rehabilitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adhesive capsulitis of shoulder?", "answers": ["Percutaneous Ethanol Injection", "Watchful waiting", "Physical therapy", "Pyeloplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adhesive capsulitis of shoulder?", "answers": ["Ointment", "Dental restoration", "Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation", "Dextran 75"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adhesive capsulitis of shoulder?", "answers": ["Dilation and curettage", "Cholecystectomy", "Antifungal medication", "Joint manipulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Allergy?", "answers": ["Elastic bandage", "Caesarean section", "Leukotriene antagonist", "Hydroxyprogesterone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Allergy?", "answers": ["Truss", "Immunotherapy", "Gonadotropin-releasing hormone analogue", "Bed rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Liposuction", "Clear liquid diet", "Catheter ablation therapy", "Diphenidol"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "Iridectomy", "Validation therapy", "Liposomal doxorubicin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scoliosis?", "answers": ["Minimally Invasive Thorasic Spinal Fusion", "Cervical conization", "Nutrition", "Calcium levulinate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scoliosis?", "answers": ["Chiropractic treatment techniques", "Move patient to cool area", "Psychotherapy", "Pyeloplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scoliosis?", "answers": ["Warm soak", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Panretinal Photocoagulation", "Back brace"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scoliosis?", "answers": ["Oral rehydration therapy", "Selective estrogen-receptor modulator", "Physical exercise", "Iridectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scoliosis?", "answers": ["Electrical muscle stimulation", "Tympanostomy tube", "Bedrest", "Cryotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rotator cuff tear?", "answers": ["Penile prosthesis", "Simulated presence therapy", "Cryosurgery", "Arthroscopy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rotator cuff tear?", "answers": ["Childbirth", "Alpha-adrenergic agonist", "Arthroplasty", "Arthrocentesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rotator cuff tear?", "answers": ["Chlorhexidine", "Hygiene", "Bifocals", "Steroid"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myocardial Ischemia?", "answers": ["Esophagogastrectomy", "PUVA therapy", "Scleral buckle", "Angioplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myocardial Ischemia?", "answers": ["Vicks VapoRub", "Percutaneous coronary intervention", "Physical exercise", "Anti-asthmatic Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myocardial Ischemia?", "answers": ["Coronary stent", "Mechanical ventilation", "Modifying Phonation Intervals (MPI)", "Hearing aid"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Plantar wart?", "answers": ["Light therapy", "Counseling psychology", "Cryotherapy", "Glasses"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Plantar wart?", "answers": ["Percutaneous nephrolithotomy", "Stereotactic radiation therapy", "Urinary catheterization", "Soft-tissue laser surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Plantar wart?", "answers": ["Validation therapy", "Needle aponeurotomy", "Enema", "Cauterization"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ventricular tachycardia?", "answers": ["POWERade", "Eye surgery", "Electrical muscle stimulation", "Defibrillation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ventricular tachycardia?", "answers": ["Catheter ablation therapy", "Bowel resection", "Elevation of the legs", "Hip replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ventricular tachycardia?", "answers": ["Elastic bandage", "Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator", "Antiarrhythmic agent", "SIR-Spheres"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Proctocolectomy", "Topical medication", "Mitral valve replacement", "Percutaneous coronary intervention"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Iron supplement", "Diaphragmatic breathing", "Home blood pressure monitors", "Long-acting beta-adrenoceptor agonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lichen nitidus?", "answers": ["Catheter ablation therapy", "Debacterol", "Ultraviolet light therapy", "Respiratory therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Urethroplasty", "Urethrotomy", "Radioactive iodine therapy", "Gum depigmentation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Thyroidectomy", "Cardiac catheterization", "Eye movement desensitization and reprocessing", "Epley maneuver"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Meningeal Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Thyroidectomy", "Steroid", "Liposuction", "Hyperbaric medicine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Generalized anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Pyrethrin", "Rehabilitation", "Speech-language pathology"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Seborrheic keratosis?", "answers": ["Cryotherapy", "Alginic acid", "Cyanate", "Mastoidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Seborrheic keratosis?", "answers": ["Ureteric stent", "Group psychotherapy", "Cauterization", "Pyrethrin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Seborrheic keratosis?", "answers": ["Uvulopalatopharyngoplasty", "Cryosurgery", "Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Ketogenic diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Seborrheic keratosis?", "answers": ["Esophagogastrectomy", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist", "Curettage", "Intracytoplasmic sperm injection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Seborrheic keratosis?", "answers": ["Oral rehydration therapy", "Weight loss", "Biopsy", "Cannabis smoking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atherosclerosis?", "answers": ["Wide local excision", "Pancreatectomy", "Dextran 1", "Angioplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atherosclerosis?", "answers": ["Cyanate", "Physical exercise", "Orthomolecular medicine", "High fiber diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atherosclerosis?", "answers": ["Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Fungicide", "Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug", "Gradual increase in length and complexity of utterance (GILCU)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atherosclerosis?", "answers": ["Antacid", "Cochlear implant", "Antiplatelet drug", "Sunscreen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ingrown hair?", "answers": ["Validation therapy", "Median sternotomy", "Warm compress", "Cox maze procedure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Microcephaly?", "answers": ["Cannabis smoking", "Splint", "Mustargen Oncovin Procarbazine Prednisone", "Occupational therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Microcephaly?", "answers": ["Reminiscence therapy", "Speech-language pathology", "Tuberculosis management", "Increase fluid intake"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Microcephaly?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Immersion in cool water", "Physical therapy", "Cardioversion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Non-small cell lung cancer?", "answers": ["Cervical conization", "Radiation therapy", "Immersion in cool water", "Pulmonary artery catheter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Non-small cell lung cancer?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "Liver dialysis", "Surgical Drain", "Laser therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Non-small cell lung cancer?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Calcium Carbonate", "Chlorhexidine", "Trioxsalen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Quadriplegia?", "answers": ["Continuous positive airway pressure", "Mitral valve replacement", "Traction", "Mastoidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Quadriplegia?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Guanadrel", "Cochlear implant", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatomyositis?", "answers": ["Eyepatch", "Immunosuppressive drug", "Westmead Program", "Lactase"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatomyositis?", "answers": ["Intravenous immunoglobulin", "Heart transplantation", "Negative-pressure wound therapy", "Tuboplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatomyositis?", "answers": ["Move patient to cool area", "Rest", "Intrastromal corneal ring segments", "Delayed auditory feedback"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatomyositis?", "answers": ["High fiber diet", "Truss", "Enema", "Physical exercise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatomyositis?", "answers": ["Calcium levulinate", "Rubber band ligation", "Elastic bandage", "Orthosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatomyositis?", "answers": ["Moisturizer", "Laxative", "Ileostomy", "LASIK"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatomyositis?", "answers": ["surgery", "Immersion in cool water", "Thyroid Agent", "Group psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatomyositis?", "answers": ["Dextran 75", "Incision and drainage", "Renal replacement therapy", "Heat therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatomyositis?", "answers": ["Ointment", "Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy", "Ambulatory phlebectomy", "Fungicide"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatomyositis?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Passive immunity", "Bismuth subgallate", "Thyroglobulin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Panretinal Photocoagulation", "Nicotine withdrawal", "Edmonton protocol", "Garlic oil"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Trimethoprim-Sulfamethoxazole", "Antiviral drug", "Physical exercise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Left atrial appendage occlusion", "Cryotherapy", "Defibrillator", "Blood glucose monitoring"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Stanford V", "Fasciotomy", "Percutaneous nephrolithotomy", "Pancreas transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Antifungal medication", "Diabetic diet", "Anti-asthmatic Agent", "Immunosuppressive drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pneumothorax?", "answers": ["Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate", "Mechanical ventilation", "Amputation", "Plasmapheresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pneumothorax?", "answers": ["Artificial tears", "Chest tube", "Orthokeratology", "Laxative"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gestational diabetes?", "answers": ["Ignipuncture", "Orabase B", "Atrial septostomy", "Physical exercise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gestational diabetes?", "answers": ["Diet high in omega-3-fatty acids", "Cardioversion", "Microvascular decompression", "Diabetic diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Psoriasis?", "answers": ["Massage", "Ultraviolet light therapy", "Eye surgery", "Synovectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Psoriasis?", "answers": ["Watchful waiting", "Antihypotensive agent", "Laser radial keratotomy", "Excimer laser"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Psoriasis?", "answers": ["Trioxsalen", "Vitamin E", "Radical retropubic prostatectomy", "Electrical muscle stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Psoriasis?", "answers": ["Therapeutic endoscopy", "PUVA therapy", "Arthrocentesis", "Synovectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Olestra", "Vitamin C", "Carbohydrate", "Iron supplement"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Warm compress", "Laser therapy", "Family Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Blood transfusion", "Uterine artery embolization", "Vacuum aspiration", "Topical steroid"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bone metastasis?", "answers": ["Ignipuncture", "Light therapy", "Trioxsalen", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Neurogenic bladder dysfunction?", "answers": ["Bismuth subgallate", "Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator", "Kegel exercise", "Radioactive iodine therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Neurogenic bladder dysfunction?", "answers": ["Surgery", "COPP-ABVD Regimen", "Myringotomy", "Percutaneous nephrolithotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Neurogenic bladder dysfunction?", "answers": ["Urinary catheterization", "Vein stripping", "DizzyFIX", "Smoking cessation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Electroconvulsive therapy", "Blood transfusion", "Clear liquid diet", "Orthosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Androgen replacement therapy", "Diet high in omega-3-fatty acids", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Pyeloplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Smoking cessation", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Stereotactic radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Rehabilitation", "Westmead Program", "Dextran 1", "Appendectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Psychoeducation", "Family Therapy", "Tracheotomy", "Warm soak"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Cognitive remediation therapy for schizophrenia", "Low-carbohydrate diet", "Dietary supplement"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Orthomolecular medicine", "Ear cleaning", "Tympanoplasty", "Laxative"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Avascular necrosis?", "answers": ["Exposure therapy", "Blood transfusion", "Osteotomy", "Sex reassignment surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Avascular necrosis?", "answers": ["Joint replacement", "High caloric diet", "Radiofrequency ablation", "Penile prosthesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Avascular necrosis?", "answers": ["Orthopedic cast", "Physical exercise", "Steroidal ophthalmic drops", "Bone grafting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diabetes insipidus?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "Fontan procedure", "Fluency shaping", "Negative-pressure wound therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diabetes insipidus?", "answers": ["Edmonton protocol", "Repronex", "Autologous", "Increase fluid intake"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kawasaki disease?", "answers": ["Angioplasty", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Nicotine withdrawal", "Corneal transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kawasaki disease?", "answers": ["Rehydration", "Wide local excision", "Intravenous immunoglobulin", "Chloroethane"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kawasaki disease?", "answers": ["Conception device", "Hip replacement", "Coronary stent", "Hip replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kawasaki disease?", "answers": ["Circumcision", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Ketogenic diet", "Combined oral contraceptive pill"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Leriche Technique", "Intravenous therapy", "Calcium Carbonate", "Bed rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Appendectomy", "Pyloromyotomy", "Laser radial keratotomy", "High-intensity focused ultrasound"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Trigeminal neuralgia?", "answers": ["Cholinesterase inhibitor", "Lotion", "Antiviral drug", "Stereotactic radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Trigeminal neuralgia?", "answers": ["Oral rehydration therapy", "Frequency-altered auditory feedback", "Radial keratotomy", "Microvascular decompression"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Contact lens", "Warm soak", "Low-carbohydrate diet", "Therapeutic endoscopy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Norwood procedure", "Dextran 75", "Pergonal", "Lobectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Immunotherapy", "Surgery", "Vacuum aspiration", "Sunscreen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Stapled hemorrhoidopexy", "Physical exercise", "Contact lens", "Cataract surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for HELLP syndrome?", "answers": ["Immunosuppressive drug", "Sunscreen", "Hospitalization", "Chemotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for HELLP syndrome?", "answers": ["Fontan procedure", "Childbirth", "Palliative care", "Nasal irrigation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for HELLP syndrome?", "answers": ["Debridement", "Bedrest", "Pneumatic Retinopexy", "Dietary fiber"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for HELLP syndrome?", "answers": ["Abstinence", "Blood transfusion", "Tuberculosis management", "Bronchodilator"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ventricular septal defect?", "answers": ["Cardiac catheterization", "Gradual increase in length and complexity of utterance (GILCU)", "Ignipuncture", "Clear liquid diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ventricular septal defect?", "answers": ["Tendonectomy", "Median sternotomy", "Salpingectomy", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Mastoiditis?", "answers": ["Home blood pressure monitors", "Subtotal Parathyroidectomy", "Myringotomy", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Mastoiditis?", "answers": ["Mastoidectomy", "Massage", "Calcium levulinate", "Nightmare Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Keratitis?", "answers": ["Long-acting beta-adrenoceptor agonist", "Cataract surgery", "Deep brain stimulation", "Antifungal medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Keratitis?", "answers": ["Watchful waiting", "Mitrofanoff appendicovesicostomy", "Antibiotic ophthalmic drops", "Tracheotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Keratitis?", "answers": ["Fontan procedure", "Antiviral drug", "Myringotomy", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tinnitus?", "answers": ["PUVA therapy", "Panretinal Photocoagulation", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Turbinectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Ketogenic diet", "Cannabis smoking", "Surgery", "In vitro fertilization"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Carbuncle?", "answers": ["Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator", "Hygiene", "Adrenalectomy", "Proctocolectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Carbuncle?", "answers": ["Proper hygiene", "Chlorhexidine", "High carbohydrate diet", "External beam radiotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Carbuncle?", "answers": ["Defibrillator", "Calamine", "Bronchodilator", "Warm compress"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myopia?", "answers": ["Renal replacement therapy", "Delayed auditory feedback", "Radial keratotomy", "Mustargen Oncovin Procarbazine Prednisone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myopia?", "answers": ["Orthomolecular medicine", "Contact lens", "Dextrothyroxine", "Depigmentation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myopia?", "answers": ["Stretching", "Refractive surgery", "Long-acting beta-adrenoceptor agonist", "Frequency-altered auditory feedback"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myopia?", "answers": ["Smoking cessation", "Bed rest", "LASIK", "Heart transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myopia?", "answers": ["Sensory integration", "Ointment", "Defibrillation", "Orthokeratology"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myopia?", "answers": ["Tracheotomy", "Occupational therapy", "Move patient to cool area", "Glasses"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tennis elbow?", "answers": ["Physical exercise", "Nerve block", "Patellar tendon strap", "Nasal spray"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tennis elbow?", "answers": ["Cholinesterase inhibitor", "Orthosis", "Ignipuncture", "Massage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tennis elbow?", "answers": ["Pancreas transplantation", "Sclerotherapy", "Low sodium diet", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hip fracture?", "answers": ["Hip replacement", "Chiropractic treatment techniques", "Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Lithotripsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Conjunctivitis?", "answers": ["Endovenous laser treatment", "Zoster-immune globulin", "Ear drop", "Eye drop"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Conjunctivitis?", "answers": ["Artificial tears", "Laminectomy", "Bed rest", "Topical steroid"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Electroconvulsive therapy", "Radiation therapy", "Animal-assisted therapy", "Corneal transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Enucleation of the eye", "Dextran 75", "Chemotherapy", "COPP-ABVD Regimen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Radial keratotomy", "Sun protective clothing", "Surgery", "Nerve block"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Pharmacotherapy", "Defibrillator", "In vitro fertilization", "Vitamin C"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["LASIK", "Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator", "Cyanate", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Olestra", "Arthroscopy", "Dietary fiber", "Percutaneous coronary intervention"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Nasal spray", "Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Vitamin B Complex", "Cardiac catheterization"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Vagal maneuver", "Coronary stent", "Diet high in omega-3-fatty acids", "Caesarean section"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Furuncle?", "answers": ["Intracardiac repair", "Warm compress", "Ketogenic diet", "Trabeculectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Ignipuncture", "Cardiac pacemaker", "Hydrotherapy", "Proctocolectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Mitrofanoff appendicovesicostomy", "Skin grafting", "Scleral buckle", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Laser coagulation", "Pegylated Interferon Alfa", "Parathyroidectomy", "Ketogenic diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Continuous positive airway pressure", "Cryotherapy", "Trauma Group Therapy", "Bone grafting"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Vitrectomy", "Cauterization", "Traction", "Urethrotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Mastectomy", "Sclerotherapy", "Defibrillation", "Pneumatic Retinopexy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Trigger finger?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Vein stripping", "Corneal transplantation", "Salpingectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Trigger finger?", "answers": ["Radical perineal prostatectomy", "Mitral valve replacement", "Percutaneous trigger finger release", "Cardiac catheterization"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Trigger finger?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Oophorectomy", "Transference focused psychotherapy", "Osteotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Trigger finger?", "answers": ["Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator", "Splint", "Childbirth", "Educational Support Professional"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Trigger finger?", "answers": ["Rest", "Antiflatulent", "Orabase B", "Biopsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Body dysmorphic disorder?", "answers": ["Counseling", "Amputation", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Laminectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tricuspid atresia?", "answers": ["Blalock\u2013Taussig shunt", "Brachytherapy", "Cerivastatin Sodium", "Carotid endarterectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tricuspid atresia?", "answers": ["Mitral valve repair", "Dietary supplement", "Atrial septostomy", "Tympanoplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tricuspid atresia?", "answers": ["Oral rehydration therapy", "Fontan procedure", "Defibrillation", "Tympanoplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Meningitis?", "answers": ["Increase fluid intake", "Transurethral resection of the prostate", "Radiation therapy", "Erythritol tetranitrate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Meningitis?", "answers": ["Conductive keratoplasty", "Stroke recovery", "Rest", "Defibrillator"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Meningitis?", "answers": ["Compression stockings", "Cryosurgery", "Intravenous therapy", "Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Vitiligo?", "answers": ["Cannabis smoking", "Skin grafting", "Radiosurgery", "Iron supplement"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Vitiligo?", "answers": ["Dietary fiber", "Mitral valve repair", "Diphtheria anti-toxin", "Depigmentation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Vitiligo?", "answers": ["Passive immunity", "Ureteric stent", "In vitro fertilization", "PUVA therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Vitiligo?", "answers": ["Hemodialysis", "Dilation and evacuation", "Angioplasty", "Trioxsalen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Vitiligo?", "answers": ["Intracytoplasmic sperm injection", "Tendonectomy", "Autologous", "Tendonectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Barrett's esophagus?", "answers": ["Mitral valve repair", "Nissen fundoplication", "Tympanostomy tube", "Vagus nerve stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Barrett's esophagus?", "answers": ["Radiofrequency ablation", "Cough medicine", "Warm soak", "Pyloromyotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Barrett's esophagus?", "answers": ["Anticonvulsant", "Laser therapy", "Esophagectomy", "Rehabilitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Barrett's esophagus?", "answers": ["Depigmentation", "Photodynamic therapy", "Scleral buckle", "Marsupialization"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Human papillomavirus infection?", "answers": ["Panretinal Photocoagulation", "Antiviral drug", "Dietary supplement", "Soft-tissue laser surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Human papillomavirus infection?", "answers": ["Fluid replacement", "Surgery", "Ablation", "Antacid"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Human papillomavirus infection?", "answers": ["Stretching", "Edmonton protocol", "Cryotherapy", "Genioglossus advancement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Human papillomavirus infection?", "answers": ["Cauterization", "Oral rehydration therapy", "Home blood pressure monitors", "Suprapubic cystostomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Peyronie's disease?", "answers": ["Vein stripping", "Vitamin E", "Cryosurgery", "Electrical muscle stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Peyronie's disease?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Patellar tendon strap", "Garlic oil", "Interpersonal psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Peyronie's disease?", "answers": ["Aminobenzoate Potassium", "surgery", "Cancer immunotherapy", "Hydroxyprogesterone"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Peyronie's disease?", "answers": ["Nesbit plication", "Heat therapy", "Nail avulsion", "Lactase"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Peyronie's disease?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Lidcombe Program", "Leriche Technique", "Orthopedic cast"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Peyronie's disease?", "answers": ["Penile prosthesis", "Selective estrogen-receptor modulator", "Pyeloplasty", "Barrier cream"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypocalcaemia?", "answers": ["Fasciotomy", "Calcium levulinate", "Proctosedyl", "POWERade"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Intussusception?", "answers": ["Enema", "High fiber diet", "Narcotic", "Cold compression therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Intussusception?", "answers": ["Myringotomy", "Counseling", "Intravenous therapy", "Liver dialysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cushing's syndrome?", "answers": ["Neurectomy", "Antihypotensive agent", "Adrenalectomy", "Salpingectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cushing's syndrome?", "answers": ["Animal-assisted therapy", "Pancreas transplantation", "Knee Joint Aspiration", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cushing's syndrome?", "answers": ["Warm soak", "Surgery", "Massage", "Cefaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Macular degeneration?", "answers": ["Soft-tissue laser surgery", "Phacoemulsification", "Photodynamic therapy", "Reminiscence therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Macular degeneration?", "answers": ["Monoclonal Antibody Anti-VEGF", "Parathyroidectomy", "Dialectical behavior therapy", "Patellar tendon strap"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Macular degeneration?", "answers": ["Endovenous laser treatment", "Excimer laser", "Microvascular decompression", "Laser coagulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Macular degeneration?", "answers": ["Delayed auditory feedback", "Ear cleaning", "Antioxidant", "Anti-diabetic medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stye?", "answers": ["Low sodium diet", "Joint manipulation", "Antiviral drug", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stye?", "answers": ["Epidural Steroid Injection", "Iridectomy", "Tonsillectomy", "Proper hygiene"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stye?", "answers": ["Hormone therapy", "Esophagectomy", "Laser", "Warm compress"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Postpartum thyroiditis?", "answers": ["Liver dialysis", "Eye surgery", "Urethroplasty", "Thyroid Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acanthosis nigricans?", "answers": ["Nail avulsion", "Antihypotensive agent", "Erythritol tetranitrate", "Laser therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acanthosis nigricans?", "answers": ["Kidney transplantation", "Dermabrasion", "Histamine antagonist", "Immunosuppressant"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Peritonitis?", "answers": ["Cerivastatin Sodium", "Kegel exercise", "Radical perineal prostatectomy", "Laparotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Peritonitis?", "answers": ["Narcotic", "Photorefractive keratectomy", "Rehabilitation", "Traction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Peritonitis?", "answers": ["Orabase B", "Liver dialysis", "Vitamin B Complex", "Intravenous therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hirschsprung's disease?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Ileostomy", "Orthosis", "High carbohydrate diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hirschsprung's disease?", "answers": ["Alcohol detoxification", "Esophagogastrectomy", "Colostomy", "Antiplatelet drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bacillary dysentery?", "answers": ["Retroperitoneal lymph node dissection", "Smoking cessation", "Bismuth subgallate", "Childbirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Psychosis?", "answers": ["Percutaneous balloon valvotomy", "Family Therapy", "Moisturizer", "Dialectical behavior therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Psychosis?", "answers": ["Dextran 40", "Thymectomy", "Photodynamic therapy", "Animal-assisted therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Psychosis?", "answers": ["Immunosuppressant", "Self-limiting", "Elevation of the legs", "Electroconvulsive therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Psychosis?", "answers": ["Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Cannabis smoking", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate", "Cold compression therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Eclampsia?", "answers": ["Caesarean section", "Nerve block", "Stenting", "Low sodium diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypospadias?", "answers": ["Excimer laser", "Surgery", "Wide local excision", "Conductive keratoplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypospadias?", "answers": ["Simulated presence therapy", "In vitro fertilization", "Frequency-altered auditory feedback", "Circumcision"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alcohol abuse?", "answers": ["Plasmapheresis", "Sex reassignment surgery", "Abstinence", "Calcium levulinate"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alcohol abuse?", "answers": ["Thrombolytic drug", "Erythritol tetranitrate", "Group psychotherapy", "Appendectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alcohol abuse?", "answers": ["Antibacterial soap", "Support group", "Interpersonal psychotherapy", "Vitrectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alcohol abuse?", "answers": ["Alcohol detoxification", "Long-acting beta-adrenoceptor agonist", "Gluten-free diet", "Thymectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Delayed sleep phase disorder?", "answers": ["Lobectomy", "Oophorectomy", "Surgery", "Light therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Encephalitis?", "answers": ["Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation", "Home blood pressure monitors", "Rest", "Electroconvulsive therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Encephalitis?", "answers": ["Circumcision", "Antiflatulent", "Fluid replacement", "Deep brain stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Encephalitis?", "answers": ["Adrenalectomy", "Stroke recovery", "Antiviral drug", "Dietary supplement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Encephalitis?", "answers": ["Pergonal", "Anticonvulsant", "Sun protective clothing", "Cervical conization"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tuberculous cervical lymphadenitis?", "answers": ["Animal-assisted therapy", "Diet high in omega-3-fatty acids", "Oxygen therapy", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tuberculous cervical lymphadenitis?", "answers": ["Tuberculosis management", "Westmead Program", "Westmead Program", "Anti-asthmatic Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Aphasia?", "answers": ["High fiber diet", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Patellar tendon strap", "Mitral valve repair"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Aphasia?", "answers": ["Iron supplement", "Leriche Technique", "Transcranial direct-current stimulation", "Iron supplement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiac arrhythmia?", "answers": ["Speech-language pathology", "Cardioversion", "EndoCinch endoluminal gastroplication", "Intravenous immunoglobulin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiac arrhythmia?", "answers": ["Potassium permanganate", "Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation", "Vicks VapoRub", "Vagal maneuver"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiac arrhythmia?", "answers": ["Educational Support Professional", "Kegel exercise", "Defibrillation", "Prostate brachytherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cardiac arrhythmia?", "answers": ["Enucleation of the eye", "Antiarrhythmic agent", "Orthomolecular medicine", "Capsaicin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Glomerulonephritis?", "answers": ["Low sodium diet", "Plasmapheresis", "Electrical muscle stimulation", "Lotion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Glomerulonephritis?", "answers": ["Angiotensin II receptor antagonist", "Potassium permanganate", "Dextran 75", "Mastectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Burn?", "answers": ["Alginic acid", "Lactase", "Prostate brachytherapy", "Penile prosthesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Burn?", "answers": ["Dextran 40", "Percutaneous nephrolithotomy", "Family Therapy", "Escharotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Burn?", "answers": ["Skin grafting", "Phototherapeutic keratectomy", "Scleral buckle", "Electroconvulsive therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Burn?", "answers": ["Occupational therapy", "Tuboplasty", "Rehydration", "Nissen fundoplication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Placental abruption?", "answers": ["Blood transfusion", "Cefaly", "Dextrothyroxine", "Continuous positive airway pressure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Placental abruption?", "answers": ["Anti-diabetic medication", "Caesarean section", "Laminotomy", "Elastic bandage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Placental abruption?", "answers": ["Intra-aortic balloon pump", "Intravenous therapy", "Pyrethrin", "High carbohydrate diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dupuytren's contracture?", "answers": ["Warm soak", "Laminotomy", "Complete fasciectomy", "Ureteric stent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dupuytren's contracture?", "answers": ["Fasciotomy", "Turbinectomy", "Selective estrogen-receptor modulator", "Arthrocentesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dupuytren's contracture?", "answers": ["Left Ventricular Assist Device", "Fluency shaping", "Partial fasciectomy", "Androgen replacement therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dupuytren's contracture?", "answers": ["Animal-assisted therapy", "Needle aponeurotomy", "Management of HIV/AIDS", "surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dysentery?", "answers": ["Uterine artery embolization", "Thoracentesis", "Photorefractive keratectomy", "Oral rehydration therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dysentery?", "answers": ["Phacoemulsification", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist", "Intravenous therapy", "Speech-language pathology"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dysentery?", "answers": ["Hemodialysis", "Biologic", "Increase fluid intake", "Renal replacement therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dysentery?", "answers": ["Rehydration", "Thrombectomy", "Aortic valve replacement", "Sunscreen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bursitis?", "answers": ["Gradual increase in length and complexity of utterance (GILCU)", "Physical therapy", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Hygiene"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bursitis?", "answers": ["Physical examination", "Trabeculoplasty", "Laminotomy", "Rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bursitis?", "answers": ["Modifying Phonation Intervals (MPI)", "Steroid", "Hormone therapy", "Cochlear implant"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bursitis?", "answers": ["Cold compression therapy", "Psychoeducation", "Liposuction", "Liposuction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pertussis?", "answers": ["Bowel resection", "Coronary stent", "Turbinectomy", "Trimethoprim-Sulfamethoxazole"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Fluency shaping", "Dental restoration", "Biofeedback", "Chemotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Radiation therapy", "Mechanical ventilation", "Immunosuppressant", "Pulmonary Valve Replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Eye drop", "Surgery", "Mitral valve replacement", "Mastectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Kegel exercise", "Ice pack", "Pancreatectomy", "High-protein diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Westmead Program", "Stress management", "Pancreaticoduodenectomy", "Speech-language pathology"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Colorectal polyp?", "answers": ["DizzyFIX", "Ambulatory phlebectomy", "Adrenalectomy", "Polypectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Colorectal polyp?", "answers": ["Dilation and curettage", "Proctocolectomy", "Fluency shaping", "Erythritol tetranitrate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Colorectal polyp?", "answers": ["Educational Support Professional", "Traction", "Colectomy", "Sanitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Head and neck cancer?", "answers": ["Radiation therapy", "Photorefractive keratectomy", "Appendectomy", "Laxative"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atopic dermatitis?", "answers": ["Ultraviolet light therapy", "Fluency shaping", "Massage", "High-intensity focused ultrasound"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atopic dermatitis?", "answers": ["Lobectomy", "Sodium hyaluronate", "Monoclonal Antibody Anti-VEGF", "Dermabrasion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adenomyosis?", "answers": ["Chlorhexidine", "Oxygen therapy", "Physical medicine and rehabilitation", "Hormone therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adenomyosis?", "answers": ["Palliative care", "Percutaneous nephrolithotomy", "Hysterectomy", "Iron supplement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Pyloromyotomy", "Anger management", "Diphtheria anti-toxin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Laser coagulation", "Cardioversion", "Aminobenzoate Potassium", "Photodynamic therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Defibrillation", "Eyepatch", "Alkali salt", "Phacoemulsification"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Nasal irrigation", "Norwood procedure", "Blood transfusion", "Percutaneous coronary intervention"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Thrombolytic drug", "Vagus nerve stimulation", "Nail avulsion", "Anti-diabetic medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urethritis?", "answers": ["Aminobenzoate Potassium", "Therapeutic endoscopy", "Hygiene", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urethritis?", "answers": ["Hemodialysis", "Cancer immunotherapy", "Cough medicine", "Abstinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Noonan syndrome?", "answers": ["Carbohydrate", "Sulfacytine", "Speech-language pathology", "Parathyroidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Noonan syndrome?", "answers": ["Stretching", "Endometrial ablation", "Photodynamic therapy", "Physical therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Noonan syndrome?", "answers": ["Oxygen therapy", "Surgery", "Synovectomy", "Increase fluid intake"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Sensory integration", "Relaxation technique", "Thrombolytic drug", "Sunscreen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Urethrotomy", "Simulated presence therapy", "Enema", "Pulmonary rehabilitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Orthokeratology", "Radiosurgery", "Vitamin E", "Bismuth subgallate"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Polypectomy", "Contact lens", "Reminiscence therapy", "Minimally Invasive Thorasic Spinal Fusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Lung transplantation", "Deep brain stimulation", "Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator", "Validation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Brachytherapy", "Laparoscopic radical prostatectomy", "Low-fat diet", "Esophagectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adenoid cystic carcinoma?", "answers": ["Cryoablation", "Adjuvant", "Hysterectomy", "Conception device"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adenoid cystic carcinoma?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Anticonvulsant", "Lung transplantation", "Interpersonal psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adenoid cystic carcinoma?", "answers": ["Post-exposure prophylaxis", "Fast neutron therapy", "Oxygen therapy", "Hysterectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adenoid cystic carcinoma?", "answers": ["Orthokeratology", "Defibrillation", "Leriche Technique", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Adenoid cystic carcinoma?", "answers": ["External beam radiotherapy", "Childbirth", "Balloon  valvuloplasty", "Repronex"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pain?", "answers": ["Alpha-adrenergic agonist", "Carotid endarterectomy", "Embolization", "Chloroethane"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myxedema?", "answers": ["Fluid replacement", "Panretinal Photocoagulation", "Diaphragmatic breathing", "Thyroglobulin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Contact dermatitis?", "answers": ["Oxygen therapy", "Calamine", "Tuberculosis management", "Intracardiac repair"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Angelman syndrome?", "answers": ["Androgen replacement therapy", "Gluten-free diet", "Physical therapy", "Antiarrhythmic agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Angelman syndrome?", "answers": ["Drug detoxification", "Ointment", "Interpersonal psychotherapy", "Speech-language pathology"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Angelman syndrome?", "answers": ["Ear drop", "Anticonvulsant", "Tonsillectomy", "Bowel resection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Angelman syndrome?", "answers": ["Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Trabeculectomy", "Microvascular decompression", "Applied behavior analysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Electroconvulsive therapy", "Tonsillectomy", "Conductive keratoplasty", "Prosthesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Applied behavior analysis", "Barrier cream", "Skin grafting", "Tracheotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Enema", "Splint", "Genioglossus advancement", "Trioxsalen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Chloroethane", "Continuous positive airway pressure", "Hysterectomy", "Diphtheria anti-toxin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Hormone replacement therapy", "Prosthesis", "Pulmonary rehabilitation", "Maxillomandibular advancement"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Pharmacotherapy", "Uvulopalatopharyngoplasty", "Median sternotomy", "Enema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["POWERade", "Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug", "Turbinectomy", "Circumcision"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Pancreatectomy", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Hernia repair", "Vitamin E"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Phototherapeutic keratectomy", "Abstinence", "Electroconvulsive therapy", "Minimally Invasive Thorasic Spinal Fusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Rest", "Tuboplasty", "Vitamin C"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver cancer?", "answers": ["Dietary fiber", "SIR-Spheres", "Fontan procedure", "Frequency-altered auditory feedback"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Leukemia?", "answers": ["Heart transplantation", "Radiation therapy", "Ureteric stent", "Transurethral resection of the prostate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Leukemia?", "answers": ["Respiratory therapy", "Ultraviolet light therapy", "Chemotherapy", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Leukemia?", "answers": ["Counseling psychology", "Immunotherapy", "Pentaerythritol", "Move patient to cool area"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Leukemia?", "answers": ["Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Low-fat diet", "High carbohydrate diet", "Radioactive iodine therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Nasal congestion?", "answers": ["Pergonal", "Tuboplasty", "Fontan procedure", "Vicks VapoRub"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Liver transplantation", "Triethylenetetramine", "Cancer immunotherapy", "External beam radiotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Antiviral drug", "Mitral valve replacement", "Fluency shaping", "Transurethral microwave thermotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Pulmonary artery catheter", "Retroperitoneal lymph node dissection", "Steroid", "Angioplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Hip replacement", "Ear drop", "Mastoidectomy", "Alginic acid"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Ear cleaning", "Turbinectomy", "Norwood procedure", "Self-limiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Prosthesis", "Thrombolytic drug", "Antifungal medication", "Ultraviolet light therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Depression?", "answers": ["Mitral valve replacement", "Orthomolecular medicine", "Dextran 1", "Surgical Drain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urethral stricture?", "answers": ["Vitamin C", "Gradual increase in length and complexity of utterance (GILCU)", "Suprapubic cystostomy", "Nil per os"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urethral stricture?", "answers": ["Endometrial ablation", "Ureteroscopic stone removal", "Laser therapy", "Mitrofanoff appendicovesicostomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urethral stricture?", "answers": ["Capsaicin", "Marsupialization", "Iron supplement", "Urethroplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urethral stricture?", "answers": ["Cholecystectomy", "Urethrotomy", "Exposure therapy", "Trifocal lenses"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atrial septal defect?", "answers": ["Cardiac catheterization", "Narcotic", "Dental restoration", "Lung transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atrial septal defect?", "answers": ["Respiratory therapy", "Psychotherapy", "Cardiac surgery", "Intrastromal corneal ring segments"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Necrotizing fasciitis?", "answers": ["Debridement", "Phacoemulsification", "Polypectomy", "Transsphenoidal surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Necrotizing fasciitis?", "answers": ["Negative-pressure wound therapy", "Thrombolytic drug", "Stretching", "Cancer immunotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Necrotizing fasciitis?", "answers": ["Amputation", "Intrastromal corneal ring segments", "Endoscopic thoracic sympathectomy", "Ureteric stent"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Necrotizing fasciitis?", "answers": ["Intracytoplasmic sperm injection", "Hyperbaric medicine", "Occupational therapy", "Mohs surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder?", "answers": ["Cardioversion", "Psychotherapy", "Ketogenic diet", "Interpersonal psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder?", "answers": ["Pentaerythritol", "Bariatric surgery", "Support group", "Negative-pressure wound therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder?", "answers": ["Orabase B", "Patellar tendon strap", "Orabase B", "Family Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Delayed auditory feedback", "Norwood procedure", "Stress management", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Diaphragmatic breathing", "Anger management", "Gatorade", "Electroconvulsive therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Prosthesis", "Lotion", "Psychotherapy", "Continuous positive airway pressure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lordosis?", "answers": ["Educational Support Professional", "Triethylenetetramine", "Orabase B", "Orthosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lordosis?", "answers": ["Interpersonal psychotherapy", "Traction", "Assisted reproductive technology", "Physical therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lordosis?", "answers": ["Physical exercise", "Left Ventricular Assist Device", "Needle aponeurotomy", "Cannabis smoking"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kyphosis?", "answers": ["Spinal surgery", "Salpingectomy", "Laparotomy", "Passive immunity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kyphosis?", "answers": ["Hormone therapy", "Fungicide", "Physical exercise", "Cholinesterase inhibitor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kyphosis?", "answers": ["Orthosis", "Nightmare Therapy", "Cyanate", "Polypectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kwashiorkor?", "answers": ["Bonjela", "Dermabrasion", "Hydrotherapy", "High caloric diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kwashiorkor?", "answers": ["Left atrial appendage occlusion", "High-protein diet", "Photodynamic therapy", "PUVA therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kwashiorkor?", "answers": ["Cerivastatin Sodium", "Endovenous laser treatment", "Gene therapy", "Dietary supplement"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Hormone therapy", "Appendectomy", "Electrolysis", "Radial keratotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Endovenous laser treatment", "Nerve block", "Hysterectomy", "Cefaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Bed rest", "Vitamin B Complex", "Combined oral contraceptive pill", "Hip replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Hydroxyprogesterone", "Graded exercise therapy", "Counseling", "Pyloromyotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Breastfeeding", "Endovascular coiling", "Carbohydrate", "Oophorectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Spinal cord stimulator", "Pharmacotherapy", "Pancreas transplantation", "Laparoscopic surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Heartburn?", "answers": ["Dilation and curettage", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate", "Alkali salt", "Adjuvant"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Dialectical behavior therapy", "Endometrial ablation", "Polypectomy", "Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Transference focused psychotherapy", "High-protein diet", "Coronary stent", "Eyepatch"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Heart valve disease?", "answers": ["Cancer immunotherapy", "Aortic valve replacement", "Blood transfusion", "Alcohol detoxification"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Heart valve disease?", "answers": ["Surgical Drain", "Photorefractive keratectomy", "Inguinal orchiectomy", "Percutaneous balloon valvotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Heart valve disease?", "answers": ["Intraocular lens", "Tuboplasty", "High carbohydrate diet", "Mitral valve replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Heart valve disease?", "answers": ["Urinary catheterization", "Cardiac catheterization", "Fungicide", "Antiarrhythmic agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Heart valve disease?", "answers": ["Nasal irrigation", "Mitral valve repair", "Dermabrasion", "Applied behavior analysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Soft-tissue laser surgery", "Increase fluid intake", "Edmonton protocol", "Mohs surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Rest", "Genioglossus advancement", "Pyloromyotomy", "Animal-assisted therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Salmonellosis?", "answers": ["Hormone therapy", "Self-limiting", "Orthopedic cast", "Delayed auditory feedback"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Necrobiosis lipoidica?", "answers": ["Intrastromal corneal ring segments", "Cauterization", "Educational Support Professional", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anterior cruciate ligament injury?", "answers": ["Eyepatch", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Splint", "Antifungal medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anterior cruciate ligament injury?", "answers": ["Leukotriene antagonist", "Cold compression therapy", "Antiandrogen", "Partial fasciectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anterior cruciate ligament injury?", "answers": ["Oophorectomy", "Elastic bandage", "Proctosedyl", "LASIK"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anterior cruciate ligament injury?", "answers": ["Rehabilitation", "Proper hygiene", "Anti-asthmatic Agent", "Physical medicine and rehabilitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anterior cruciate ligament injury?", "answers": ["Dextrothyroxine", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Ice pack", "Endovascular aneurysm repair"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anterior cruciate ligament injury?", "answers": ["Reconstructive surgery", "Nutrition", "Biopsy", "Pulmonary artery catheter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Presbyopia?", "answers": ["Self-limiting", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate", "Uvulopalatopharyngoplasty", "Trifocal lenses"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Presbyopia?", "answers": ["Glasses", "Androgen replacement therapy", "Thoracentesis", "Phacoemulsification"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Presbyopia?", "answers": ["Laparoscopic radical prostatectomy", "Nicotine withdrawal", "Pergonal", "Photorefractive keratectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Presbyopia?", "answers": ["Endovenous laser treatment", "LASIK", "Physical exercise", "Oxygen therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Presbyopia?", "answers": ["Contact lens", "Stereotactic radiation therapy", "Dextran 40", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Presbyopia?", "answers": ["Intraocular lens", "Massage", "Olestra", "Gum depigmentation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Presbyopia?", "answers": ["Repronex", "Urethrotomy", "Conductive keratoplasty", "Gonadotropin-releasing hormone analogue"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Presbyopia?", "answers": ["Dialysis", "Pneumococcal vaccine", "Antihypotensive agent", "Bifocals"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ectodermal dysplasia?", "answers": ["Massage", "Renal replacement therapy", "Heat therapy", "Topical medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ectodermal dysplasia?", "answers": ["Endoscopic thoracic sympathectomy", "Artificial tears", "Alcohol detoxification", "Ablation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ectodermal dysplasia?", "answers": ["Chemotherapy", "Orthokeratology", "Retroperitoneal lymph node dissection", "Ice pack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acromegaly?", "answers": ["Adrenalectomy", "Sensory integration", "Transsphenoidal surgery", "Laser coagulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acromegaly?", "answers": ["Ice pack", "Salpingectomy", "Vitrectomy", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Livedo reticularis?", "answers": ["Transurethral microwave thermotherapy", "Hyperbaric medicine", "Esophagectomy", "Endovascular coiling"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Livedo reticularis?", "answers": ["Potassium permanganate", "Nail avulsion", "Dental restoration", "PUVA therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["Gradual increase in length and complexity of utterance (GILCU)", "Cardiac surgery", "Stroke recovery", "Anti-asthmatic Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["Conductive keratoplasty", "Alcohol detoxification", "Oxygen therapy", "Sclerotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["Thrombectomy", "Enucleation of the eye", "Dialectical behavior therapy", "Pyrethrin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["Dilation and evacuation", "Physical therapy", "Arthroplasty", "Immunosuppressive drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["Topical Anti-Infective Agent", "Carotid endarterectomy", "Median sternotomy", "Kegel exercise"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["Gene therapy", "Vacuum aspiration", "Laparotomy", "Thrombolytic drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["Bismuth subgallate", "Cryoablation", "Surgery", "Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["Radiosurgery", "Joint manipulation", "Rubber band ligation", "Transcranial direct-current stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["High-protein diet", "Osteotomy", "Radioactive iodine therapy", "Angioplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["Occupational therapy", "Ear drop", "Proctocolectomy", "Orthomolecular medicine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["Cognitive remediation therapy for schizophrenia", "Intravenous therapy", "Relaxation technique", "In vitro fertilization"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stroke?", "answers": ["Plasmapheresis", "Uterine artery embolization", "Laser coagulation", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sensorineural hearing loss?", "answers": ["Psychoeducation", "Incision and drainage", "Narcotic", "Cochlear implant"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sensorineural hearing loss?", "answers": ["Phacoemulsification", "Conductive keratoplasty", "Hearing aid", "Lung transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Psychoeducation", "Marsupialization", "Stenting", "Chemotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Spinal cord stimulator", "Percutaneous nephrolithotomy", "Radiation therapy", "TNF inhibitor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Symptomatic", "Throat lozenge", "Adjuvant", "Warm soak"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Nephrostomy", "Cough medicine", "Intraocular lens"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Dental restoration", "Radiofrequency ablation", "Alpha-adrenergic agonist", "Plasmapheresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Brachytherapy", "Occupational therapy", "LASIK", "Surgical Drain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Photodynamic therapy", "Diaphragmatic breathing", "Photorefractive keratectomy", "Counterirritant"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atrial fibrillation?", "answers": ["Prostate brachytherapy", "Cardioversion", "Complete fasciectomy", "Nephrostomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atrial fibrillation?", "answers": ["Left atrial appendage occlusion", "Distraction osteogenesis", "Inguinal orchiectomy", "Parathyroidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atrial fibrillation?", "answers": ["Ureteric stent", "Fungicide", "Catheter ablation therapy", "Parathyroidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atrial fibrillation?", "answers": ["Artificial tears", "Low-carbohydrate diet", "Aortic valve replacement", "Cox maze procedure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atrial fibrillation?", "answers": ["Uterine myomectomy", "Radiofrequency ablation", "SIR-Spheres", "Electrosurgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Atrial fibrillation?", "answers": ["Antiarrhythmic agent", "Needle aponeurotomy", "Splint", "EndoCinch endoluminal gastroplication"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pyoderma gangrenosum?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Topical medication", "Hyperbaric medicine", "Cognitive behavioral therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pyoderma gangrenosum?", "answers": ["Epidural Steroid Injection", "Nasal spray", "Diabetic diet", "Immunosuppressant"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Polymyositis?", "answers": ["Ureteroscopic stone removal", "Vicks VapoRub", "Prosthesis", "Intravenous immunoglobulin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Irritable bowel syndrome?", "answers": ["Corrective lens", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent", "Back brace", "Laxative"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Irritable bowel syndrome?", "answers": ["Orthopedic surgery", "Dietary fiber", "Laser coagulation", "Dermabrasion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Antacid", "Thrombolytic drug", "Ultraviolet light therapy", "Graded exercise therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Lobectomy", "Vitamin B Complex", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Passive immunity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Cough medicine", "Stress management", "Nicotine withdrawal", "Androgen replacement therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Primary hyperparathyroidism?", "answers": ["Hernia repair", "Surgery", "Tendonectomy", "Plasmapheresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Seborrheic dermatitis?", "answers": ["Colectomy", "Pyrithione Zinc", "Kawashima procedure", "Cyanate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Impetigo?", "answers": ["Topical Anti-Infective Agent", "Orthopedic surgery", "Cefaly", "Urethroplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Nephrotic syndrome?", "answers": ["Fast neutron therapy", "External beam radiotherapy", "Sanitation", "Immunosuppressive drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Coronary artery disease?", "answers": ["Kegel exercise", "Angioplasty", "Dextrothyroxine", "Pericardiocentesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Coronary artery disease?", "answers": ["Coronary stent", "Nasal irrigation", "Polypectomy", "Patellar tendon strap"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Coronary artery disease?", "answers": ["Pyloromyotomy", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Orthosis", "Gatorade"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Avoidant personality disorder?", "answers": ["Symptomatic", "Psychotherapy", "Cognitive therapy", "Glasses"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Avoidant personality disorder?", "answers": ["Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Antiplatelet drug", "Endometrial ablation", "Arthroplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Avoidant personality disorder?", "answers": ["Cancer immunotherapy", "Stroke recovery", "Group psychotherapy", "Negative-pressure wound therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dyshidrosis?", "answers": ["Lidcombe Program", "Cold compression therapy", "Surgery", "Counterirritant"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dyshidrosis?", "answers": ["Biopsy", "Vitamin E", "Tonsillectomy", "Potassium permanganate"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kaposi's sarcoma?", "answers": ["Clear liquid diet", "Management of HIV/AIDS", "Potassium permanganate", "Hearing aid"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kaposi's sarcoma?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Skin grafting", "Chemotherapy", "Nasal spray"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kaposi's sarcoma?", "answers": ["Defibrillator", "Diabetic diet", "Chest tube", "Photodynamic therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kaposi's sarcoma?", "answers": ["Moisturizer", "Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy", "Immunotherapy", "Occupational therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kaposi's sarcoma?", "answers": ["Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Ointment", "Hearing aid", "Rehabilitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kaposi's sarcoma?", "answers": ["Neurectomy", "Hygiene", "Radiation therapy", "Leukotriene antagonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kaposi's sarcoma?", "answers": ["Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Inguinal orchiectomy", "POWERade", "Cryosurgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Tonsillectomy", "Frequency-altered auditory feedback", "Dextrothyroxine", "Thyroidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Increase fluid intake", "Oral rehydration therapy", "Tuboplasty", "Antiplatelet drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Transcranial direct-current stimulation", "Nicotine withdrawal", "Triethylenetetramine", "Throat lozenge"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Hormone replacement therapy", "Percutaneous coronary intervention", "Atrial septostomy", "Rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Balloon  valvuloplasty", "Diaphragmatic breathing", "Maxillomandibular advancement", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Intra-aortic balloon pump", "Kidney transplantation", "Cholinesterase inhibitor", "Nissen fundoplication"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Partial fasciectomy", "Mitrofanoff appendicovesicostomy", "Antacid", "Narcotic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Renal replacement therapy", "EndoCinch endoluminal gastroplication", "Capsaicin", "Graded exercise therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Autologous", "Prokinetic agent", "Cold compression therapy", "Depigmentation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Proctosedyl", "Alginic acid", "Intravenous therapy", "Bed rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "Pyrethrin", "Stretta system", "Bedrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hyperopia?", "answers": ["Pulmonary Valve Replacement", "Excimer laser", "Glasses", "Pancreatectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hydatidiform mole?", "answers": ["Antacid", "Laser coagulation", "Radial keratotomy", "Hysterectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hydatidiform mole?", "answers": ["Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Ear drop", "Dilation and curettage", "Clipping"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hydatidiform mole?", "answers": ["Joint manipulation", "Mitral valve repair", "Curettage", "Left atrial appendage occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypochondriasis?", "answers": ["Psychoeducation", "Needle aponeurotomy", "Deep brain stimulation", "Cox maze procedure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypochondriasis?", "answers": ["Pergonal", "Kawashima procedure", "Bedrest", "Cognitive behavioral therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Coronary artery bypass surgery", "TNF inhibitor", "Hydrodilatation", "Sclerotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Synovectomy", "Hysterectomy", "In vitro fertilization", "Anti-asthmatic Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Intra-aortic balloon pump", "Ultraviolet light therapy", "COPP-ABVD Regimen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Arthroplasty", "Percutaneous Ethanol Injection", "Increase fluid intake", "Antiviral drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Catheter ablation therapy", "Thyroglobulin", "Laparoscopic surgery", "Immunosuppressive drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug", "Debacterol", "Median sternotomy", "Radical perineal prostatectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myocarditis?", "answers": ["Nerve block", "Endoscopic thoracic sympathectomy", "Chlorhexidine", "Heart transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myocarditis?", "answers": ["Turbinectomy", "Hearing aid", "Rest", "Uvulopalatopharyngoplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Myocarditis?", "answers": ["Intra-aortic balloon pump", "Warm soak", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist", "Dextran 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Somatoform disorder?", "answers": ["Corneal transplantation", "Pergonal", "Spinal surgery", "Cognitive behavioral therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Patent ductus arteriosus?", "answers": ["High caloric diet", "Inguinal orchiectomy", "Bismuth subgallate", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scarlet fever?", "answers": ["Light therapy", "Increase fluid intake", "Cardioversion", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Scarlet fever?", "answers": ["Rest", "Ventricular assist device", "Radioactive iodine therapy", "Frequency-altered auditory feedback"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Nasal spray", "Compression stockings", "Norwood procedure", "Cyanate"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Histamine antagonist", "Truss", "Hyperbaric medicine", "Antacid"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Autoimmune thyroiditis?", "answers": ["Thrombectomy", "Skin grafting", "Hip replacement", "Thyroglobulin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Irritant diaper dermatitis?", "answers": ["Pneumococcal vaccine", "Patellar tendon strap", "Ambulatory phlebectomy", "Barrier cream"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Irritant diaper dermatitis?", "answers": ["Uterine myomectomy", "Hydroxyprogesterone", "Antifungal medication", "Osteotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Irritant diaper dermatitis?", "answers": ["Fast neutron therapy", "Catheter ablation therapy", "Proper hygiene", "Norwood procedure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Uveitis?", "answers": ["Chiropractic treatment techniques", "Steroidal ophthalmic drops", "Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Inguinal orchiectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Endovascular aneurysm repair", "Artificial tears", "Self-limiting", "Tuberculosis management"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Smoking cessation", "Needle aponeurotomy", "Rehydration", "Thyroidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Yellow fever?", "answers": ["Eye drop", "Palliative care", "Pulmonary Valve Replacement", "Debridement"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hirsutism?", "answers": ["Antiandrogen", "Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation", "Proctosedyl", "Cancer immunotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hirsutism?", "answers": ["Gatorade", "Caesarean section", "Barrier cream", "Electrolysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Relaxation technique", "High-intensity focused ultrasound", "Delayed auditory feedback", "Refractive surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Ileostomy", "Cryotherapy", "Psychotherapy", "Bismuth subgallate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Stapled hemorrhoidopexy", "Laser", "External beam radiotherapy", "Vagal maneuver"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Hormone therapy", "Simulated presence therapy", "Caesarean section", "Incision and drainage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Fast neutron therapy", "Hydrodilatation", "Vagus nerve stimulation", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Pancreas transplantation", "Relaxation technique", "Cryosurgery", "Exposure therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "Endometrial ablation", "Laparoscopic radical prostatectomy", "Incision and drainage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Palliative care", "Epidural Steroid Injection", "High fiber diet", "Narcotic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Post-exposure prophylaxis", "Implanted cardiac resynchronization device", "Watchful waiting", "Sanitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Sclerotherapy", "Transcranial direct-current stimulation", "Radical perineal prostatectomy", "Pyloromyotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Pancreaticoduodenectomy", "Pentaerythritol", "Radical retropubic prostatectomy", "Speech-language pathology"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Liver transplantation", "Liver transplantation", "Chemotherapy", "Trauma Group Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Arthroplasty", "Cognitive remediation therapy for schizophrenia", "Gene therapy", "Zoster-immune globulin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Refractive surgery", "Narcotic", "Prostate brachytherapy", "Myringotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gallstone?", "answers": ["Oophorectomy", "Loop electrical excision procedure", "Group psychotherapy", "Lithotripsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gallstone?", "answers": ["Cryotherapy", "Childbirth", "Cholecystectomy", "Cranberry juice"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gallstone?", "answers": ["Negative-pressure wound therapy", "Relaxation technique", "Educational Support Professional", "Laparoscopic surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gallstone?", "answers": ["Therapeutic endoscopy", "In vitro fertilization", "High caloric diet", "Counseling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Anti-diabetic medication", "Cough medicine", "Vein stripping", "Laparoscopic surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Intra-aortic balloon pump", "Watchful waiting", "Negative-pressure wound therapy", "Blood glucose monitoring"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Immunosuppressant", "Escharotomy", "Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation", "Smoking cessation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Dilation and evacuation", "Immunosuppressive drug", "EndoCinch endoluminal gastroplication", "Physical examination"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Uterine myomectomy", "Diabetic diet", "Lithotripsy", "Cold compression therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Nesbit plication", "Percutaneous nephrolithotomy", "Physical exercise", "Circumcision"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cataract?", "answers": ["Topical steroid", "Endovenous laser treatment", "Complete fasciectomy", "Phacoemulsification"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cataract?", "answers": ["Radiosurgery", "Ileostomy", "Sunscreen", "Cataract surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Bed rest", "Support group", "Laser coagulation", "Compression stockings"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stuttering?", "answers": ["Alginic acid", "Frequency-altered auditory feedback", "Transurethral needle ablation of the prostate", "Turbinectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stuttering?", "answers": ["Combined oral contraceptive pill", "Ileostomy", "Diaphragmatic breathing", "Antifungal medication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stuttering?", "answers": ["Pericardiocentesis", "Endoscopic thoracic sympathectomy", "Delayed auditory feedback", "Proctocolectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stuttering?", "answers": ["Gradual increase in length and complexity of utterance (GILCU)", "Electrical muscle stimulation", "Laminotomy", "Uvulopalatopharyngoplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stuttering?", "answers": ["Steroid", "Fluency shaping", "POWERade", "Mohs surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stuttering?", "answers": ["Westmead Program", "Radioactive iodine therapy", "Enema", "Thymectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stuttering?", "answers": ["Turbinectomy", "Lidcombe Program", "Carotid endarterectomy", "Percutaneous coronary intervention"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Stuttering?", "answers": ["Pyeloplasty", "Ureteroscopic stone removal", "Cardiac monitoring", "Modifying Phonation Intervals (MPI)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Binge eating disorder?", "answers": ["Interpersonal psychotherapy", "Ignipuncture", "Immersion in cool water", "Special education"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Binge eating disorder?", "answers": ["Transsphenoidal surgery", "Stereotactic radiation therapy", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Kawashima procedure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Trachoma?", "answers": ["Nightmare Therapy", "Surgery", "Eye drop", "Physical examination"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Trachoma?", "answers": ["Thyroglobulin", "Proper hygiene", "Bedrest", "Debacterol"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Trachoma?", "answers": ["Sanitation", "Special education", "Narcotic", "Exposure therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bartholin's cyst?", "answers": ["Zoster-immune globulin", "Marsupialization", "Antiviral drug", "Cholecystectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bartholin's cyst?", "answers": ["Surgical Drain", "Brachytherapy", "Microvascular decompression", "Sun protective clothing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Goitre?", "answers": ["Partial Thyroidectomy", "Arthroscopy", "Topical steroid", "Special education"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Goitre?", "answers": ["Hydrodilatation", "Trioxsalen", "Transurethral microwave thermotherapy", "Radioactive iodine therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Goitre?", "answers": ["Trimethoprim-Sulfamethoxazole", "Thyroidectomy", "Angioplasty", "Osteotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Goitre?", "answers": ["Thymectomy", "Biofeedback", "Thyroglobulin", "Laparotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Endometrial cancer?", "answers": ["Knee Joint Aspiration", "Combined oral contraceptive pill", "Suprapubic cystostomy", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Endometrial cancer?", "answers": ["Ventricular assist device", "Stenting", "LASIK", "Hormone therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Endometrial cancer?", "answers": ["Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy", "Surgery", "Thrombectomy", "Mastoidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Endometrial cancer?", "answers": ["Phototherapeutic keratectomy", "Enema", "Gluten-free diet", "Chemotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cellulitis?", "answers": ["Hyperbaric medicine", "High carbohydrate diet", "Partial fasciectomy", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cellulitis?", "answers": ["Debridement", "Chlorhexidine", "Urinary catheterization", "Sensory integration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Seasonal affective disorder?", "answers": ["Hydrodilatation", "Psychotherapy", "Fluid replacement", "Esophagogastrectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Seasonal affective disorder?", "answers": ["Graded exercise therapy", "Light therapy", "Ice pack", "Massage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anemia?", "answers": ["Dietary supplement", "Debacterol", "In vitro fertilization", "Circumcision"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anemia?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "High-intensity focused ultrasound", "Orthomolecular medicine", "Enema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anemia?", "answers": ["Bone grafting", "Family Therapy", "Dextran 1", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anemia?", "answers": ["Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug", "Tendonectomy", "Iron supplement", "Median sternotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anemia?", "answers": ["Bronchodilator", "Acupuncture", "Pyloromyotomy", "Blood transfusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anemia?", "answers": ["Pneumococcal vaccine", "Dietary fiber", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Conception device"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Shock?", "answers": ["Patellar tendon strap", "Dextrothyroxine", "Dextran 1", "Artificial tears"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Shock?", "answers": ["Dextran 40", "Narcotic", "Bismuth subgallate", "Diet high in omega-3-fatty acids"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Shock?", "answers": ["Modifying Phonation Intervals (MPI)", "Dextran 75", "Needle aponeurotomy", "Nesbit plication"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Emphysema?", "answers": ["Vagus nerve stimulation", "Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy", "Gonadotropin-releasing hormone analogue", "Steroid"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Emphysema?", "answers": ["Joint manipulation", "Sun protective clothing", "Bronchodilator", "Trauma Group Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Guanadrel", "Cognitive therapy", "Cardiac monitoring", "Cochlear implant"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Home blood pressure monitors", "POWERade", "Hydrodilatation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Transurethral resection of the prostate", "Westmead Program", "Endovascular aneurysm repair", "Enucleation of the eye"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Relaxation technique", "Mitrofanoff appendicovesicostomy", "Palliative care", "Intravenous therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Photorefractive keratectomy", "Antiarrhythmic agent", "Antiplatelet drug", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Keratoconus?", "answers": ["Antihypotensive agent", "Ablation", "Contact lens", "Polypectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Keratoconus?", "answers": ["High-intensity focused ultrasound", "Corneal transplantation", "Anti-diabetic medication", "Dialysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Keratoconus?", "answers": ["Aortic valve replacement", "Cardiac surgery", "Radial keratotomy", "Radiofrequency ablation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Keratoconus?", "answers": ["Thymectomy", "Intrastromal corneal ring segments", "Cochlear implant", "Group psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Keratoconus?", "answers": ["Laser radial keratotomy", "Nightmare Therapy", "Trifocal lenses", "Intracytoplasmic sperm injection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Stretching", "Cancer immunotherapy", "Urethrotomy", "Ice pack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Low-fat diet", "Cryoablation", "Hernia repair", "Move patient to cool area"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Symptomatic", "Tendonectomy", "Immersion in cool water", "Back brace"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Amputation", "Abstinence", "Skin grafting", "Rehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Immunosuppressive drug", "Nil per os", "Transurethral needle ablation of the prostate", "Vitrectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Urethrotomy", "Incision and drainage", "Uterine artery embolization", "Intravenous therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Narcotic", "Sanitation", "Cardioversion", "Immersion in cool water"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Counterirritant", "Colostomy", "Cryotherapy", "Balloon  valvuloplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Reconstructive surgery", "Clear liquid diet", "Enema", "Sensory integration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Arthrocentesis", "Bowel resection", "Orthopedic surgery", "Physical therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gynecomastia?", "answers": ["Pergonal", "Liposuction", "Counterirritant", "Chloroethane"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gynecomastia?", "answers": ["Mastectomy", "Adrenalectomy", "Retroperitoneal lymph node dissection", "Trifocal lenses"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gynecomastia?", "answers": ["Iridectomy", "Wide local excision", "Edmonton protocol", "Androgen replacement therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pityriasis rosea?", "answers": ["Sanitation", "Bifocals", "Cataract surgery", "Ultraviolet light therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pityriasis rosea?", "answers": ["Topical steroid", "Gatorade", "Myringotomy", "Nutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Sunscreen", "Orthokeratology", "Gene therapy", "Transference focused psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Anti-asthmatic Agent", "Androgen replacement therapy", "Increase fluid intake", "Refractive surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Defibrillator", "Colectomy", "Anti-asthmatic Agent", "Lung transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy", "Passive immunity", "Bronchodilator", "Hydroxyprogesterone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Splint", "Vagus nerve stimulation", "Pneumococcal vaccine", "Vein stripping"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Physical exercise", "Respiratory therapy", "Vagal maneuver", "Urinary catheterization"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prader\u2013Willi syndrome?", "answers": ["Ketogenic diet", "Bariatric surgery", "Tonsillectomy", "Psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prader\u2013Willi syndrome?", "answers": ["Hormone therapy", "Hyperbaric medicine", "Physical exercise", "Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prader\u2013Willi syndrome?", "answers": ["Nail avulsion", "Mitral valve replacement", "Physical therapy", "Trioxsalen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prader\u2013Willi syndrome?", "answers": ["Nutrition", "Transsphenoidal surgery", "Continuous positive airway pressure", "Patellar tendon strap"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prader\u2013Willi syndrome?", "answers": ["Speech-language pathology", "Conductive keratoplasty", "Narcotic", "Negative-pressure wound therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Hospitalization", "Cochlear implant", "Radical perineal prostatectomy", "Chest tube"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Plantar fasciitis?", "answers": ["Clear liquid diet", "Bowel resection", "Extracorporeal shockwave therapy", "Blood glucose monitoring"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Plantar fasciitis?", "answers": ["Westmead Program", "Caesarean section", "Surgery", "Chlorhexidine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Plantar fasciitis?", "answers": ["Nil per os", "Cox maze procedure", "Physical therapy", "Pulmonary Valve Replacement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Plantar fasciitis?", "answers": ["Splint", "Immunosuppressant", "Debacterol", "Heart transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteochondritis dissecans?", "answers": ["Dextran 40", "Modifying Phonation Intervals (MPI)", "PUVA therapy", "Orthosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteochondritis dissecans?", "answers": ["Corneal transplantation", "Nasal irrigation", "Physical therapy", "LASIK"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteochondritis dissecans?", "answers": ["Percutaneous coronary intervention", "Debridement", "Rest", "Ultraviolet light therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteochondritis dissecans?", "answers": ["Arthroscopy", "Childbirth", "Home blood pressure monitors", "Tonsillectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Alginic acid", "Atrial septostomy", "Intravenous therapy", "Respiratory therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Retroperitoneal fibrosis?", "answers": ["Extracorporeal shockwave therapy", "Immunosuppressant", "Aminobenzoate Potassium", "Leukotriene antagonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Retroperitoneal fibrosis?", "answers": ["Liver transplantation", "Surgery", "Urethroplasty", "TNF inhibitor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Conversion disorder?", "answers": ["Dental restoration", "Mustargen Oncovin Procarbazine Prednisone", "Physical therapy", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Conversion disorder?", "answers": ["Percutaneous balloon valvotomy", "Psychotherapy", "Tracheotomy", "Depigmentation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Conversion disorder?", "answers": ["Distraction osteogenesis", "Nightmare Therapy", "Photorefractive keratectomy", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Benign paroxysmal positional vertigo?", "answers": ["DizzyFIX", "Vasoconstrictor", "Alginic acid", "Diabetic diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Benign paroxysmal positional vertigo?", "answers": ["Epley maneuver", "Anti-asthmatic Agent", "Esophagectomy", "Carotid endarterectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Rest", "Lidcombe Program", "Pancreas transplantation", "Biologic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Trifocal lenses", "Leukotriene antagonist", "Antiviral drug", "Biologic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Pulmonary artery catheter", "Thrombolytic drug", "Increase fluid intake", "Amputation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Fibromyalgia?", "answers": ["Electrolysis", "Arthroscopy", "Intra-aortic balloon pump", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Multiple myeloma?", "answers": ["Thymectomy", "Radiation therapy", "Antioxidant", "Nil per os"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Multiple myeloma?", "answers": ["Anti-diabetic medication", "Nasal irrigation", "Chemotherapy", "Pancreaticoduodenectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Multiple myeloma?", "answers": ["Atrial septostomy", "Intra-aortic balloon pump", "Combined oral contraceptive pill", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Paget's disease of bone?", "answers": ["Validation therapy", "Zoster-immune globulin", "Surgery", "Drug detoxification"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Sodium hyaluronate", "Topical medication", "Distraction osteogenesis", "Percutaneous nephrolithotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Contact lens", "Mechanical ventilation", "Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy", "Microvascular decompression"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Bifocals", "Tracheotomy", "Ureteroscopic stone removal", "Defibrillation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Ventricular assist device", "Cardiac monitoring", "Electrosurgery", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bacterial arthritis?", "answers": ["Polypectomy", "Rest", "Enucleation of the eye", "Ureteroscopic stone removal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bacterial arthritis?", "answers": ["Physical exercise", "Relaxation technique", "Pericardiocentesis", "Hormone therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bacterial arthritis?", "answers": ["Percutaneous balloon valvotomy", "Laminotomy", "Physical therapy", "Vacuum aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Bacterial arthritis?", "answers": ["Scleral buckle", "Sulfacytine", "Arthrocentesis", "Dextran 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Common cold?", "answers": ["Vicks VapoRub", "Fluency shaping", "Stroke recovery", "Traction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Common cold?", "answers": ["Rubber band ligation", "Diphenidol", "Hydroxyprogesterone", "Cough medicine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Common cold?", "answers": ["Catheter ablation therapy", "Stroke recovery", "Rest", "Gonadotropin-releasing hormone analogue"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Common cold?", "answers": ["Increase fluid intake", "Gum depigmentation", "Drug detoxification", "EndoCinch endoluminal gastroplication"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Common cold?", "answers": ["Ear cleaning", "Pulmonary Valve Replacement", "Mycophenolate Mofetil", "Symptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Follicular thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Simulated presence therapy", "Left atrial appendage occlusion", "Cerivastatin Sodium", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Follicular thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Chemotherapy", "Rehabilitation", "Photodynamic therapy", "Alkali salt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Follicular thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Antiarrhythmic agent", "Post-exposure prophylaxis", "Throat lozenge", "Radioactive iodine therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Follicular thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Caesarean section", "Surgery", "Fluid replacement", "Back brace"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Follicular thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Low-protein diet", "Orthokeratology", "Hormone therapy", "Rehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Erectile dysfunction?", "answers": ["Penile prosthesis", "Thrombolytic drug", "Hysterectomy", "Eye movement desensitization and reprocessing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ptosis?", "answers": ["Applied behavior analysis", "Corneal transplantation", "Debridement", "Artificial tears"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ptosis?", "answers": ["Antiviral drug", "Chemotherapy", "Turbinectomy", "Eye surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Nephritis?", "answers": ["Immunosuppressant", "Antifungal medication", "Simulated presence therapy", "Carotid endarterectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Transposition of the great arteries?", "answers": ["Percutaneous trigger finger release", "Conception device", "Liposomal doxorubicin", "Cardiac surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Transposition of the great arteries?", "answers": ["Atrial septostomy", "Electrolysis", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate", "Nil per os"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prepatellar bursitis?", "answers": ["Immunosuppressant", "Antibiotic ophthalmic drops", "Tympanoplasty", "Knee Joint Aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Prepatellar bursitis?", "answers": ["Negative-pressure wound therapy", "Physical therapy", "Calcium levulinate", "In vitro fertilization"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypercholesterolemia?", "answers": ["Carbohydrate", "COPP-ABVD Regimen", "Dextrothyroxine", "Pyloromyotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypercholesterolemia?", "answers": ["Cerivastatin Sodium", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent", "Transurethral needle ablation of the prostate", "Chemotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver tumour?", "answers": ["Cognitive therapy", "Cryosurgery", "Proper hygiene", "Cold compression therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver tumour?", "answers": ["EndoCinch endoluminal gastroplication", "Dihydroxyaluminum sodium carbonate", "Lithotripsy", "Percutaneous Ethanol Injection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver tumour?", "answers": ["Cryoablation", "Dental restoration", "Tympanostomy tube", "Thyroidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver tumour?", "answers": ["High caloric diet", "Arthroplasty", "Hydrodilatation", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver tumour?", "answers": ["Colectomy", "Low-fat diet", "Surgery", "Group psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver tumour?", "answers": ["Ice pack", "Transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation", "Radiofrequency ablation", "Family Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver tumour?", "answers": ["Chemotherapy", "Thyroid Agent", "Electroconvulsive therapy", "Ice pack"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver tumour?", "answers": ["Bone grafting", "Chlorhexidine", "Liver transplantation", "Nil per os"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver tumour?", "answers": ["Cryotherapy", "Arthroplasty", "Tuberculosis management", "Dextran 40"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver tumour?", "answers": ["Lactase", "Chemoembolization", "Ventricular assist device", "Pericardiocentesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Glaucoma?", "answers": ["Biopsy", "Radial keratotomy", "Trabeculoplasty", "Abstinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Glaucoma?", "answers": ["Laparotomy", "Dietary supplement", "Iridectomy", "Patellar tendon strap"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Glaucoma?", "answers": ["Trabeculectomy", "Ablation", "Caesarean section", "Guanadrel"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Glaucoma?", "answers": ["Cefaly", "Angiotensin II receptor antagonist", "Ointment", "Cannabis smoking"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Rehydration", "Sclerotherapy", "Edmonton protocol", "Chemotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Phototherapeutic keratectomy", "Sodium hyaluronate", "POWERade", "Alcohol detoxification"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "Hip replacement", "Pyrethrin", "Curettage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Traction", "Low-carbohydrate diet", "Oophorectomy", "Gatorade"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Combined oral contraceptive pill", "Joint replacement", "Leukotriene antagonist", "Trimethoprim-Sulfamethoxazole"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Thyroiditis?", "answers": ["Clipping", "Bedrest", "Ignipuncture", "Cauterization"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Laminectomy", "Liposomal doxorubicin", "Pancreatectomy", "Dental restoration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Corneal transplantation", "Trabeculectomy", "Dialysis", "Chemotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Urethroplasty", "Radiation therapy", "Calcium levulinate", "Gatorade"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Compression stockings", "Monoclonal Antibody Anti-VEGF", "Surgery", "Cognitive behavioral therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Graves' disease?", "answers": ["Thyroidectomy", "Pneumatic Retinopexy", "Circumcision", "Heart transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diphtheria?", "answers": ["Diphtheria anti-toxin", "Alcohol detoxification", "Tracheotomy", "Endovascular coiling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Marchiafava-Bignami disease?", "answers": ["Antiandrogen", "Oxygen therapy", "Alcohol detoxification", "Nicotine withdrawal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Marchiafava-Bignami disease?", "answers": ["Liposomal doxorubicin", "Lithotripsy", "Zoster-immune globulin", "Rehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tinea cruris?", "answers": ["Negative-pressure wound therapy", "Splint", "Fungicide", "Ureteric stent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tinea cruris?", "answers": ["Vitrectomy", "Antifungal medication", "Biologic", "Cognitive behavioral therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Somatization disorder?", "answers": ["Stereotactic radiation therapy", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Orthomolecular medicine", "Cranberry juice"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Pergonal", "Cognitive therapy", "Simulated presence therapy", "Physical medicine and rehabilitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Blood glucose monitoring", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Cervical conization", "Adrenalectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Mycophenolate Mofetil", "Breastfeeding", "Eye movement desensitization and reprocessing", "Lactase"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Cefaly", "Lobectomy", "Trauma Group Therapy", "Urinary catheterization"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Exposure therapy", "Fluid replacement", "Percutaneous Ethanol Injection", "DizzyFIX"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Transsphenoidal surgery", "Electroconvulsive therapy", "Cardiac monitoring", "Nightmare Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Negative-pressure wound therapy", "Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Liposomal doxorubicin", "Genioglossus advancement"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pilonidal cyst?", "answers": ["Mastoidectomy", "Incision and drainage", "Nissen fundoplication", "Transurethral microwave thermotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pilonidal cyst?", "answers": ["Immersion in cool water", "Surgery", "Arthroscopy", "Percutaneous Ethanol Injection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pilonidal cyst?", "answers": ["Aminobenzoate Potassium", "Excimer laser", "Marsupialization", "Alcohol detoxification"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pilonidal cyst?", "answers": ["Implantable cardioverter-defibrillator", "Graded exercise therapy", "Turbinectomy", "Warm compress"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dementia?", "answers": ["Intraocular lens", "Cholinesterase inhibitor", "Partial Thyroidectomy", "Vacuum aspiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pulmonary valve stenosis?", "answers": ["Endovascular aneurysm repair", "Hysterectomy", "Pulmonary Valve Replacement", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pulmonary valve stenosis?", "answers": ["Low-protein diet", "Iridectomy", "Deep brain stimulation", "Balloon  valvuloplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pulmonary valve stenosis?", "answers": ["Cardiac surgery", "Simulated presence therapy", "Cryotherapy", "Steroid"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pericarditis?", "answers": ["Cryotherapy", "Pericardiocentesis", "Chlorhexidine", "Abstinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pericarditis?", "answers": ["Bonjela", "Fungicide", "Cardiac surgery", "Amputation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Pericarditis?", "answers": ["Adjuvant", "Sunscreen", "Sanitation", "Steroid"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Balloon  valvuloplasty", "Surgery", "Pericardiocentesis", "Ice pack"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Kidney transplantation", "Electrosurgery", "Electrolysis", "Bronchodilator"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Patellar tendon strap", "Triethylenetetramine", "Liver transplantation", "Pulmonary rehabilitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diabetic retinopathy?", "answers": ["Plasmapheresis", "Blood glucose monitoring", "Self-limiting", "Vitrectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diabetic retinopathy?", "answers": ["Laser coagulation", "Fungicide", "Antacid", "Sulfacytine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Diabetic retinopathy?", "answers": ["Educational Support Professional", "Hospitalization", "Kawashima procedure", "Panretinal Photocoagulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypoplastic left heart syndrome?", "answers": ["Dietary fiber", "Fontan procedure", "Garlic oil", "Physical exercise"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypoplastic left heart syndrome?", "answers": ["Palliative care", "Norwood procedure", "Oral rehydration therapy", "Westmead Program"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypoplastic left heart syndrome?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Kawashima procedure", "Laser radial keratotomy", "Maxillomandibular advancement"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypoplastic left heart syndrome?", "answers": ["Radical perineal prostatectomy", "Cryotherapy", "Heart transplantation", "Caesarean section"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hyperpigmentation?", "answers": ["Gum depigmentation", "Laminectomy", "Refractive surgery", "Sun protective clothing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dyslexia?", "answers": ["Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Low-protein diet", "Educational Support Professional", "Alginic acid"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Usher syndrome?", "answers": ["Lung transplantation", "Electrosurgery", "Calcium Carbonate", "Gene therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Smoking cessation", "Rehabilitation", "Nasal spray", "Light therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["High fiber diet", "Carotid endarterectomy", "SIR-Spheres", "Laminotomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sacroiliitis?", "answers": ["Speech-language pathology", "Rest", "Physical therapy", "Topical Anti-Infective Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Actinic keratosis?", "answers": ["Thyroidectomy", "Laser therapy", "Tuboplasty", "Proctosedyl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Actinic keratosis?", "answers": ["Thyroid Agent", "Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug", "Cryosurgery", "Stanford V"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Actinic keratosis?", "answers": ["Passive immunity", "Dermabrasion", "Fluency shaping", "Mechanical ventilation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Actinic keratosis?", "answers": ["Curettage", "Cerivastatin Sodium", "Bifocals", "High-intensity focused ultrasound"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Actinic keratosis?", "answers": ["Cauterization", "Capsaicin", "Liver transplantation", "Rehabilitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Actinic keratosis?", "answers": ["Intrastromal corneal ring segments", "Tuboplasty", "Lung transplantation", "Photodynamic therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Actinic keratosis?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Passive immunity", "Pulmonary rehabilitation", "Biologic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for M\u00e9ni\u00e8re's disease?", "answers": ["Cardioversion", "Chest tube", "Intra-aortic balloon pump", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for M\u00e9ni\u00e8re's disease?", "answers": ["Steroid", "Antibacterial soap", "Lotion", "Uterine artery embolization"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for M\u00e9ni\u00e8re's disease?", "answers": ["Smoking cessation", "Blalock\u2013Taussig shunt", "Artificial tears", "Appendectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for M\u00e9ni\u00e8re's disease?", "answers": ["POWERade", "Frequency-altered auditory feedback", "Chiropractic treatment techniques", "Low sodium diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for M\u00e9ni\u00e8re's disease?", "answers": ["Rest", "Percutaneous balloon valvotomy", "Eye surgery", "Incision and drainage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Muscular dystrophy?", "answers": ["Sensory integration", "Steroidal ophthalmic drops", "Occupational therapy", "Calamine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Muscular dystrophy?", "answers": ["Renal replacement therapy", "Low-protein diet", "Cervical conization", "Orthopedic surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Muscular dystrophy?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Breastfeeding", "Ear cleaning", "Chemoembolization"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Viral meningitis?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "Leriche Technique", "Anger management", "Antioxidant"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Viral meningitis?", "answers": ["Embolization", "Percutaneous Ethanol Injection", "Increase fluid intake", "Maxillomandibular advancement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Viral meningitis?", "answers": ["Elastic bandage", "Capsaicin", "Transurethral microwave thermotherapy", "Rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Ankylosing spondylitis?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Lactase", "Pyloromyotomy", "Rubber band ligation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dwarfism?", "answers": ["Hormone therapy", "Endoscopic thoracic sympathectomy", "Cannabis smoking", "Simulated presence therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dwarfism?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Repronex", "Assisted reproductive technology", "Warm soak"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dwarfism?", "answers": ["Aortic valve replacement", "Negative-pressure wound therapy", "Distraction osteogenesis", "Hearing aid"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Vertigo?", "answers": ["Epley maneuver", "Diphtheria anti-toxin", "Autologous", "Pharmacotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Vertigo?", "answers": ["Light therapy", "Diphenidol", "Salpingectomy", "Edmonton protocol"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic Childhood Arthritis?", "answers": ["Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug", "Gradual increase in length and complexity of utterance (GILCU)", "Ice pack", "Laser coagulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypertension?", "answers": ["Garlic oil", "Photorefractive keratectomy", "Eye surgery", "Gene therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypertension?", "answers": ["Caesarean section", "Anger management", "Guanadrel", "Reminiscence therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Fibrous dysplasia of bone?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Amputation", "Stress management", "Lactase"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Secondary hyperparathyroidism?", "answers": ["Kidney transplantation", "Mitral valve repair", "Move patient to cool area", "Pyrethrin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Tetanus?", "answers": ["Frequency-altered auditory feedback", "Passive immunity", "Tympanoplasty", "Excimer laser"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatitis?", "answers": ["Synovectomy", "Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy", "Pyrithione Zinc", "Mechanical ventilation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dermatitis?", "answers": ["Calamine", "TNF inhibitor", "Aortic valve replacement", "Dialysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Frostbite?", "answers": ["Ear drop", "Amputation", "Joint manipulation", "Psychoeducation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Golfer's elbow?", "answers": ["Elastic bandage", "Liposuction", "Cognitive therapy", "Dietary fiber"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Golfer's elbow?", "answers": ["Gluten-free diet", "Cranberry juice", "Combined oral contraceptive pill", "Rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Golfer's elbow?", "answers": ["Uterine artery embolization", "POWERade", "Ice pack", "Vasoconstrictor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Golfer's elbow?", "answers": ["Dilation and curettage", "Group psychotherapy", "Stretching", "Oxygen therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Golfer's elbow?", "answers": ["Phacoemulsification", "Surgery", "Mitral valve replacement", "Complete fasciectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Cognitive behavioral therapy", "Enema", "Vitamin C", "Group psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Urethrotomy", "Colostomy", "Radiation therapy", "Chiropractic treatment techniques"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Chemotherapy", "Low-protein diet", "Potassium permanganate", "Mitral valve repair"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Transurethral needle ablation of the prostate", "Watchful waiting", "Hysterectomy", "Liver dialysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Loop electrical excision procedure", "Chemoembolization", "Assisted reproductive technology", "Immunosuppressant"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Surgery", "Electroconvulsive therapy", "Chiropractic treatment techniques", "Orthomolecular medicine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Anti-diabetic medication", "Cervical conization", "Mechanical ventilation", "Pentaerythritol"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Vagal maneuver", "Pulmonary artery catheter", "Weight loss", "Soft-tissue laser surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Orthokeratology", "Low sodium diet", "Angioplasty", "Cryosurgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Prokinetic agent", "Transference focused psychotherapy", "Surgery", "Massage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Cataract surgery", "Antacid", "Ileostomy", "Elevation of the legs"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Arthritis?", "answers": ["Diaphragmatic breathing", "Hospitalization", "Continuous positive airway pressure", "Counterirritant"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Arthritis?", "answers": ["Chemoembolization", "Gum depigmentation", "Biologic", "Vicks VapoRub"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Arthritis?", "answers": ["Post-exposure prophylaxis", "Defibrillation", "Nissen fundoplication", "Synovectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Arthritis?", "answers": ["Move patient to cool area", "Rubber band ligation", "Liposuction", "Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Arthritis?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Diphtheria anti-toxin", "Psychoeducation", "Antiandrogen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Arthritis?", "answers": ["Arthroplasty", "Orabase B", "Watchful waiting", "Dialectical behavior therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Arthritis?", "answers": ["Joint replacement", "Thyroglobulin", "Parathyroidectomy", "Transference focused psychotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Huntington's disease?", "answers": ["Occupational therapy", "Intravenous immunoglobulin", "Ultraviolet light therapy", "Endoscopic thoracic sympathectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Huntington's disease?", "answers": ["Vitrectomy", "DizzyFIX", "Speech-language pathology", "Percutaneous trigger finger release"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Patellar tendinitis?", "answers": ["Left Ventricular Assist Device", "Stretching", "External beam radiotherapy", "Low-protein diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Patellar tendinitis?", "answers": ["High caloric diet", "Patellar tendon strap", "Orthopedic surgery", "Leukotriene antagonist"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Patellar tendinitis?", "answers": ["Light therapy", "Median sternotomy", "Eye drop", "Extracorporeal shockwave therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Patellar tendinitis?", "answers": ["Stress management", "Immunotherapy", "Tendonectomy", "Stroke recovery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Patellar tendinitis?", "answers": ["Hyperbaric medicine", "Cervical conization", "Zoster-immune globulin", "Rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Patellar tendinitis?", "answers": ["Lotion", "Laparotomy", "Ice pack", "Nutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Patellar tendinitis?", "answers": ["Tympanostomy tube", "Reminiscence therapy", "Massage", "Artificial tears"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Patellar tendinitis?", "answers": ["Garlic oil", "Cancer immunotherapy", "Eye drop", "Physical therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Epilepsy?", "answers": ["Cognitive remediation therapy for schizophrenia", "Mustargen Oncovin Procarbazine Prednisone", "Orthopedic cast", "Vagus nerve stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Epilepsy?", "answers": ["Low-fat diet", "Diphtheria anti-toxin", "Circumcision", "Ketogenic diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Epilepsy?", "answers": ["Cognitive remediation therapy for schizophrenia", "Scleral buckle", "Fungicide", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Epilepsy?", "answers": ["Counseling psychology", "Cryosurgery", "Surgery", "Mitral valve repair"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Chemotherapy", "Hydroxyprogesterone", "Mechanical ventilation", "Cancer immunotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Dietary supplement", "Laser therapy", "Escharotomy", "Pharmacotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Median sternotomy", "Laparoscopic radical prostatectomy", "Antacid", "Radiation therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Antiflatulent", "Cyanate", "Enucleation of the eye", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Esophagectomy", "Clear liquid diet", "Immunotherapy", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Pentaerythritol", "Epidural Steroid Injection", "Fast neutron therapy", "Speech-language pathology"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Transurethral resection of the prostate", "Disease-modifying antirheumatic drug", "Occupational therapy", "Blood transfusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Biopsy", "surgery", "Photodynamic therapy", "Physical exercise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Tendonectomy", "Westmead Program", "Photorefractive keratectomy", "Increase fluid intake"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Splint", "Parathyroidectomy", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Symptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Physical therapy", "Rehabilitation", "Partial fasciectomy", "Pyeloplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Mitrofanoff appendicovesicostomy", "Mitral valve repair", "Deep brain stimulation", "Immunosuppressive drug"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Dystonia?", "answers": ["Mitrofanoff appendicovesicostomy", "Sunscreen", "Psychoeducation", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urolithiasis?", "answers": ["Sun protective clothing", "Family Therapy", "Esophagogastrectomy", "Nephrostomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urolithiasis?", "answers": ["Ureteric stent", "surgery", "Blood glucose monitoring", "Vasoconstrictor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urolithiasis?", "answers": ["Narcotic", "Endometrial ablation", "Pancreatectomy", "Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Trifocal lenses", "DizzyFIX", "Relaxation technique", "Photodynamic therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Thymectomy", "Weight loss", "Cannabis smoking", "Post-exposure prophylaxis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Back brace", "Epley maneuver", "Surgery", "Left Ventricular Assist Device"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Cardiac pacemaker", "Narcotic", "Synovectomy", "Genioglossus advancement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Cox maze procedure", "Ultraviolet light therapy", "Arthroplasty", "Gradual increase in length and complexity of utterance (GILCU)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Sanitation", "Physical exercise", "Alpha-adrenergic agonist", "Vicks VapoRub"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Thyroid Agent", "Mastoidectomy", "Ice pack", "Left atrial appendage occlusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Warm compress", "Compression stockings", "TNF inhibitor", "Partial Thyroidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Rest", "Low sodium diet", "Amputation", "Norwood procedure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Presbycusis?", "answers": ["Sex reassignment surgery", "Bedrest", "Liver transplantation", "Hearing aid"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic myelogenous leukemia?", "answers": ["Sclerotherapy", "Relaxation technique", "Immunotherapy", "Anti-asthmatic Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic myelogenous leukemia?", "answers": ["Steroidal ophthalmic drops", "Pharmacotherapy", "Hernia repair", "Epidural Steroid Injection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic myelogenous leukemia?", "answers": ["Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation", "Hysterectomy", "Clear liquid diet", "Barrier cream"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic myelogenous leukemia?", "answers": ["Chemotherapy", "Triethylenetetramine", "Penile prosthesis", "Iridectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Miliaria rubra?", "answers": ["Frequency-altered auditory feedback", "Alkali salt", "Genioglossus advancement", "Calamine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Miliaria rubra?", "answers": ["Complete fasciectomy", "Debridement", "Topical steroid", "Immersion in cool water"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urethral syndrome?", "answers": ["Plasmapheresis", "Coronary artery bypass surgery", "Hormone replacement therapy", "Transurethral microwave thermotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Urethral syndrome?", "answers": ["Combined oral contraceptive pill", "Alpha-adrenergic agonist", "Nissen fundoplication", "TNF inhibitor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Acute tubular necrosis?", "answers": ["Defibrillator", "Intravenous therapy", "Nightmare Therapy", "Uterine artery embolization"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Lichen planus?", "answers": ["Complete fasciectomy", "Joint replacement", "Panretinal Photocoagulation", "Light therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hypertriglyceridemia?", "answers": ["Chemoembolization", "Cerivastatin Sodium", "Stenting", "Nicotine withdrawal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Combined oral contraceptive pill", "Vitamin B Complex", "Hernia repair", "Hematopoietic stem cell transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Marasmus?", "answers": ["High-protein diet", "Light therapy", "Immunosuppressant", "Pergonal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Marasmus?", "answers": ["Counseling psychology", "Vein stripping", "Increase fluid intake", "High carbohydrate diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Marasmus?", "answers": ["Carbohydrate", "Surgical Drain", "Negative-pressure wound therapy", "Cardiac monitoring"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Spina bifida?", "answers": ["Ignipuncture", "Caesarean section", "Bonjela", "Ultraviolet light therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Spina bifida?", "answers": ["Simulated presence therapy", "High carbohydrate diet", "Sex reassignment surgery", "Surgery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sepsis?", "answers": ["Intravenous therapy", "Laser", "Alcohol detoxification", "Joint manipulation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sepsis?", "answers": ["Trifocal lenses", "Antihypotensive agent", "Enucleation of the eye", "Lidcombe Program"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Sepsis?", "answers": ["Family Therapy", "Surgery", "Gluten-free diet", "Anti-asthmatic Agent"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver failure?", "answers": ["Ear drop", "Chemotherapy", "Plasmapheresis", "Liver transplantation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver failure?", "answers": ["Thymectomy", "Cranberry juice", "Liver dialysis", "Parathyroidectomy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Liver failure?", "answers": ["Mechanical ventilation", "Trifocal lenses", "Biologic", "Biopsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Chronic pain?", "answers": ["Nissen fundoplication", "Negative-pressure wound therapy", "Transcranial magnetic stimulation", "Tympanostomy tube"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis E?", "answers": ["Circumcision", "Dermabrasion", "Radical perineal prostatectomy", "Low-protein diet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Hepatitis E?", "answers": ["Low-fat diet", "Delayed auditory feedback", "Surgery", "Alcohol detoxification"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Gender dysphoria?", "answers": ["Percutaneous nephrolithotomy", "Esophagogastrectomy", "Sex reassignment surgery", "SIR-Spheres"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a treatment for Benign prostatic hyperplasia?", "answers": ["Transurethral resection of the prostate", "Garlic oil", "Exposure therapy", "Triethylenetetramine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a treatment for Benign prostatic hyperplasia?", "answers": ["Nightmare Therapy", "Antibacterial soap", "Alpha-adrenergic agonist", "Transurethral microwave thermotherapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a treatment for Benign prostatic hyperplasia?", "answers": ["Thrombectomy", "Transurethral needle ablation of the prostate", "Conductive keratoplasty", "Urethroplasty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}